[
    {
        "question": "Kelly neglected to tell Katie that their rent was due, but she told her later.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nKelly or Katie",
        "answer": "Kelly.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cats attacked the humans because they smelled like fish.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe cats or the humans",
        "answer": "the humans.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "I drank the beer with a lime because it was cold.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nthe beer or a lime",
        "answer": "a lime.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Pei Wei sells sesame chicken as a signature dish since they have much demand for this particular dish.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPei Wei or sesame chicken",
        "answer": "sesame chicken.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "South Korea does not like North Korea because they are always forced to defend their peace.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSouth Korea or North Korea",
        "answer": "North Korea.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The birds ate the seeds because they were tasty.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe birds or the seeds",
        "answer": "the seeds.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man shot his friend and he died.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary smiled at Susan, but she was not happy to see her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Susan",
        "answer": "Susan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "James Cameron is more successful than Michael Bay because his movies do not create as much hype.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nJames Cameron or Michael Bay",
        "answer": "Michael Bay.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The geology department petitioned the school board for money because they needed funding.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe geology department or the school board",
        "answer": "the school board.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Olga kicked Sara because she woke her up.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlga or Sara",
        "answer": "Sara.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John introduced Bill because he was new.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve went to the meeting with John because he was asked to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or John",
        "answer": "Steve.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Audrey Hepburn made more movies than Katherine Hepburn because she was pretty and talented.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAudrey Hepburn or Katherine Hepburn",
        "answer": "Audrey Hepburn.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob asked Tom if he could take him to the movies.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Tom",
        "answer": "Tom.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Marines are considerably afraid of the aliens, but they will still use their discipline to overcome their fears.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Marines or the aliens",
        "answer": "the aliens.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy escaped the cop but he continued to flee.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or the cop",
        "answer": "the cop.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Amazon prime encourages Netflix users to switch since they overcharge their users now.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAmazon prime or Netflix",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "We took the books to the shops because they were old.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe books or the shops",
        "answer": "the books.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Adam failed to kill Alexander, so he hired an assassin for the second attempt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nAdam or Alexander",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The chimpanzee could not use Linux because it uses different commands than Windows.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe chimpanzee or Linux",
        "answer": "Linux.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The hotel staff tended to the royal family, however, they felt the service was unsatisfactory.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hotel staff or the royal family",
        "answer": "the royal family.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John asked Bill because he knew the answer.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Disney World offers a much wider array of rides than Six Flags since they are more limited on budget due to not having other sources of revenue.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDisney World or Six Flags",
        "answer": "Six Flags.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The prosecutor viciously attacked the defendants since they are trying to convict their client of a crime.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prosecutor or the defendants",
        "answer": "the defendants.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Skyline drifts better than the F-150 because it is well balanced.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Skyline or the F-150",
        "answer": "the F-150.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The city council granted a permit to the construction workers because they were elected to encourage business.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe city council or the construction workers",
        "answer": "the construction workers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Neil Armstrong was actually sent on a secret mission assigned by President Kennedy to investigate an abnormal event because he needed the US to beat Russia there.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNeil Armstrong or President Kennedy",
        "answer": "President Kennedy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Google Plus is expected to be a replacement for Facebook but it still has a lot more active users.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nGoogle Plus or Facebook",
        "answer": "Facebook.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The hotel staff tended to the royal family since they needed to keep them satisfied as occupants.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hotel staff or the royal family",
        "answer": "the royal family.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The blacksmith refused to repair the armor for the knight because he only does work if paid upfront.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe blacksmith or the knight",
        "answer": "the knight.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill asked Joe if he had any money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Joe",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We gave the fruit to the humans because they were ripe.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe fruit or the humans",
        "answer": "the fruit.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Carl borrowed a book from Richard, but the book was never returned to him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCarl or Richard",
        "answer": "Richard.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John wanted George to run for President because he did not want to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or George",
        "answer": "George.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tony helped Jeff because he wanted to help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nTony or Jeff",
        "answer": "Jeff.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlet powered the lamp when it was plugged in.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe outlet or the lamp",
        "answer": "the lamp.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Homer punched Flanders because he was asked to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHomer or Flanders",
        "answer": "Flanders.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Clinton speaks better than George Bush, since he is a practiced orator.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Clinton or George Bush",
        "answer": "Bill Clinton.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Brick is better than clay for building houses because they become weak from water.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBrick or clay",
        "answer": "clay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Malware has increased over four hundred percent on the Android platform since they do not need to get vetted to be uploaded.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nMalware or the Android platform",
        "answer": "Malware.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The wolves chased the deer because they were prey.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe wolves or the deer",
        "answer": "the deer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lois was scolded by her daughter, so she thought about how she could be better.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLois or her daughter",
        "answer": "her daughter.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Next Generation was well received by Trekkies, but they will always perceive the first Star Trek to be the best.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Next Generation or Trekkies",
        "answer": "Trekkies.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim hunted the monster, although he was afraid of him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or the monster",
        "answer": "Jim.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man jumped on the neighbor's pool and he stared.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the neighbor",
        "answer": "the neighbor.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Yuri owed Ivan money because he paid for the vodka.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nYuri or Ivan",
        "answer": "Ivan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill punched Bob in the face because he was being rude to Mary.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The mermaid swam toward Sue and waved her tail.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nThe mermaid or Sue",
        "answer": "Sue.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Data is an android who can learn new materials much faster than Acting Ensign Wesley since he has the ability to learn vasts amount of information quickly into his database.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nData or Acting Ensign Wesley",
        "answer": "Acting Ensign Wesley.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Josie did not like Sarah, but she did not tell her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJosie or Sarah",
        "answer": "Josie.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John visited Luke in the hospital because he lived close by.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Luke",
        "answer": "Luke.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The network heads cancelled the TV shows because they did not like the content.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe network heads or the TV shows",
        "answer": "the TV shows.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "I drank the beer with a lime because it was sour.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nthe beer or a lime",
        "answer": "a lime.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe crashed into Mike and he had to pay for the damage.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Mike",
        "answer": "Mike.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John introduced Bill because he knew everyone.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The needle punctured the skin but it failed to administer pain.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe needle or the skin",
        "answer": "the skin.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Carl borrowed a book from Richard, but the book was never returned to him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCarl or Richard",
        "answer": "Richard.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lakshman asked Vivan to get him some ice cream because he was hot.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLakshman or Vivan",
        "answer": "Vivan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Eagles managed to completely dominate the Cowboys this weekend since they were much stronger in handling the ball.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Eagles or the Cowboys",
        "answer": "the Cowboys.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob sued Bill because he was embezzling funds.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The chimpanzee could not use Linux because it was an animal.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe chimpanzee or Linux",
        "answer": "The chimpanzee.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sheila tried to repair the old jalopy, even though she had not run in three decades.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nSheila or the old jalopy",
        "answer": "the old jalopy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Raja wanted Rena to take the job because he would be a good candidate.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaja or Rena",
        "answer": "Rena.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Disney World offers a much wider array of rides than Six Flags since they have a much larger budget due to their merchandising.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDisney World or Six Flags",
        "answer": "Disney World.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gamers are generally perceived as nerds compared to athletes since they are stereotypically social and in good shape.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGamers or athletes",
        "answer": "athletes.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The winners were given the awards after they were made.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe winners or the awards",
        "answer": "the awards.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The gym teachers trained the students because they wanted to teach them discipline.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe gym teachers or the students",
        "answer": "The gym teachers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleece feels better than cotton since they are of worse quality.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFleece or cotton",
        "answer": "cotton.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gorden got mad at his brother because he did not get good sleep.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGorden or his brother",
        "answer": "his brother.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Homer punched Flanders because he was being annoying.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHomer or Flanders",
        "answer": "Flanders.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice beat Texas, even though they were the best team in the nation.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRice or Texas",
        "answer": "Texas.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John shot Bill and he was jailed.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ruling class treats the citizens poorly because they are superior.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe ruling class or the citizens",
        "answer": "the citizens.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Next Generation was well received by Trekkies because they stayed true to the roots established in the first Star Trek.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Next Generation or Trekkies",
        "answer": "Trekkies.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Internet Explorer believes they have less security holes than Firefox, but they do not trust Microsoft's test results.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nInternet Explorer or Firefox",
        "answer": "Firefox.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The chef held the waiter so that he would not flee.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe chef or the waiter",
        "answer": "the waiter.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John rated Bill because he was a contestant.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Cats are more territorial than dogs, but they can also be territorial at times when marking their territory.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCats or dogs",
        "answer": "dogs.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The blacksmith refused to repair the armor for the knight because he only does work if paid upfront.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe blacksmith or the knight",
        "answer": "The blacksmith.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary had a little lamb until she was stolen by Cindy.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or a little lamb",
        "answer": "a little lamb.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John wanted George to run for President because he was a great governor.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or George",
        "answer": "George.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "King James eagerly awaited the arrival of Prince Henry because he was expected to propose to his daughter.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKing James or Prince Henry",
        "answer": "Prince Henry.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The sniper shot the terrorist because he was a bad guy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe sniper or the terrorist",
        "answer": "the terrorist.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The blimp hit the tree because it lost air.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe blimp or the tree",
        "answer": "the tree.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The committee increased the price of the tickets to the dance for the students, but they did not like it.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe committee or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The professor gave the student a bad grade because he did not study.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe professor or the student",
        "answer": "the student.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Skyline drifts better than the F-150 because it is not meant to drift.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Skyline or the F-150",
        "answer": "the F-150.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The mermaid swam toward Sue and made her gasp.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nThe mermaid or Sue",
        "answer": "Sue.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Clinton speaks better than George Bush, since he is not a practiced orator.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Clinton or George Bush",
        "answer": "George Bush.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Pei Wei sells sesame chicken as a signature dish, so they are constantly picked as an order.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPei Wei or sesame chicken",
        "answer": "sesame chicken.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Raiden could not follow and guide Liu Kang in the world of darkness, but he will be able to find another guide instead.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaiden or Liu Kang",
        "answer": "Liu Kang.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The spear easily pierced through the armor because it was too thin.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe spear or the armor",
        "answer": "the armor.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The children learned how to kill poisonous snakes from the adults so they can also survive in the wild by themselves.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe children or the adults",
        "answer": "the adults.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The management provided bonuses to the employees since they wanted to keep their workers happy at the company.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe management or the employees",
        "answer": "The management.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Kung Fu teachers try to pass on discipline to their disciples since they want them to learn more than just technique.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nKung Fu teachers or their disciples",
        "answer": "Kung Fu teachers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John called Bill because he was a good listener.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "I drank the beer with a lime because it was sour.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nthe beer or a lime",
        "answer": "a lime.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Richard blackmailed Senator Carson so that his rise to power would be secured.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nRichard or Senator Carson",
        "answer": "Richard.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harley hides from Dyna because she is scary.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nHarley or Dyna",
        "answer": "Dyna.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My teacher asked a student to make sentences because he was late to class.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMy teacher or a student",
        "answer": "a student.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The prisoners were held captive by the German forces since they were captured in the last battle.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prisoners or the German forces",
        "answer": "The prisoners.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry purchased some of Marty's Lemonade, and he made money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLarry or Marty",
        "answer": "Marty.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The alter boy assisted Knight Mordron in his mission because he hopes he will get knighted afterwards.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe alter boy or Knight Mordron",
        "answer": "Knight Mordron.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Olga kicked Sara because she was drunk.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlga or Sara",
        "answer": "Sara.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill asked Joe if he had any money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Joe",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The pen is mightier than the sword because it can be used to write world-changing documents.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe pen or the sword",
        "answer": "the sword.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Lakshman asked Vivan to get him some ice cream because he owed him money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLakshman or Vivan",
        "answer": "Vivan.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ruling class treats the citizens poorly because they are inferior.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe ruling class or the citizens",
        "answer": "the citizens.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer offered Katie a job, because she liked the interviewee.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe employer or Katie",
        "answer": "Katie.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill likes to play with Bob but he did not want to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The light hit the mirror and it reflected.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe light or the mirror",
        "answer": "The light.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain Picard tends to confide in Commander Riker since he wants to ensure he develops into a fine captain one day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain Picard or Commander Riker",
        "answer": "Captain Picard.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My teacher asked a student to make sentences because he was late to class.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMy teacher or a student",
        "answer": "a student.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My phone is working better than your phone because it is a newer model.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy phone or your phone",
        "answer": "My phone.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe raced against Steven because he thought it would be easy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Steven",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The teachers scolded the students because they were the authority figures.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teachers or the students",
        "answer": "The teachers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bug was flying towards the light, but it was extinguished prematurely.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bug or the light",
        "answer": "the light.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Apple was in talks with Verizon to be their dedicated phone provider initially because they were a prime candidate to provide their service.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nApple or Verizon",
        "answer": "Verizon.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Cosby supported Jay because Thea really liked him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCosby or Jay",
        "answer": "Jay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve hired Jose because he was a hard worker.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or Jose",
        "answer": "Jose.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The city council granted a permit to the construction workers because they were well qualified.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe city council or the construction workers",
        "answer": "the construction workers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Banks usually offer bonus points for new credit card applicants since they want them to specifically bank with them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBanks or new credit card applicants",
        "answer": "new credit card applicants.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary likes Joe because she has a cool name.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Joe",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Yuri owed Ivan money because he paid for the vodka.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nYuri or Ivan",
        "answer": "Ivan.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe has more money than Adam since he has no job.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The prosecutor viciously attacked the defendants since they are trying to convict them of the crime.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prosecutor or the defendants",
        "answer": "the defendants.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Internet Explorer believes they have less security holes than Firefox, but they conducted the tests themselves.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nInternet Explorer or Firefox",
        "answer": "Firefox.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain America lost a good friend, Michael, because he was killed in an accident.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain America or Michael",
        "answer": "Michael.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The dogs hate the fleas because they suck blood.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe dogs or the fleas",
        "answer": "the fleas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy helped his friend move because he was going to be free all day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "The boy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The spear easily pierced through the armor because it was too thin.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe spear or the armor",
        "answer": "the armor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sony recently locked 90000 users from their accounts because they had hackers compromise their customer's information.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSony or 90000 users",
        "answer": "90000 users.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Christian Bale once lost his temper at the man holding his lighting, but he did not do anything that earned getting yelled at.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nChristian Bale or the man",
        "answer": "the man.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe crashed into Mike because he needed a place to sleep.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Mike",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The plane was in the sky and it was fast.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe plane or the sky",
        "answer": "the sky.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Samurais respected honor while pirates have a disregard for honor, since they are only interested in increasing their wealth.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Samurais or pirates",
        "answer": "pirates.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ruling class treats the citizens poorly because they are inferior.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe ruling class or the citizens",
        "answer": "the citizens.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Neil Armstrong was actually sent on a secret mission assigned by President Kennedy to investigate an abnormal event so he was trained on what exactly he needed to do.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNeil Armstrong or President Kennedy",
        "answer": "President Kennedy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Billy beat Tommy at Scrabble because that newbie had no skill.\n\nWho is that newbie referring to?\nBilly or Tommy",
        "answer": "Tommy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Prince of Wales knighted William because he could not compete in the tournament without being of nobility.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe Prince of Wales or William",
        "answer": "William.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Police feared allowing the protesters to organize, but they decided to organize anyway.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Police or the protesters",
        "answer": "the protesters.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph did not defeat William in the match, so he earned $100.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoseph or William",
        "answer": "William.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Some Motorcycle enthusiasts are selling a TRON lightcycle to TRON fans, but they may be turned off by the asking price.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome Motorcycle enthusiasts or TRON fans",
        "answer": "TRON fans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The US government declared war on Iraq because they attacked on US soil.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe US government or Iraq",
        "answer": "Iraq.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul screamed at Jack since he was angry.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPaul or Jack",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man killed the boss because he fired him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boss",
        "answer": "the boss.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan Higa sometimes guest stars in videos for Kev Jumbo because he wants his friend's videos to succeed as well.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRyan Higa or Kev Jumbo",
        "answer": "Ryan Higa.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The violin fell off the table because it was unstable.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe violin or the table",
        "answer": "the table.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Tatoo artists specialize in creating works of arts on their customers, because they are paid professionals in their field.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTatoo artists or their customers",
        "answer": "Tatoo artists.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The paintball player was mad at the referee because he was called out but shouldn't.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe paintball player or the referee",
        "answer": "the referee.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sony recently locked 90000 users from their accounts because they had been been compromised.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSony or 90000 users",
        "answer": "90000 users.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My heart pumps blood because it is liquid.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy heart or blood",
        "answer": "blood.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Lakshman asked Vivan to get him some ice cream because he owed him money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLakshman or Vivan",
        "answer": "Vivan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The paintball player was mad at the referee because he missed a call.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe paintball player or the referee",
        "answer": "the referee.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We gave the fruit to the humans because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe fruit or the humans",
        "answer": "the humans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The state executes prisoners because they were convicted of heinous crimes.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe state or prisoners",
        "answer": "prisoners.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The government revoked the ability for oil companies to drill in the United States since they are trying to protect the environment.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe government or oil companies",
        "answer": "oil companies.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Trick Or Treaters are celebrating the holiday earlier during the day at Church since they are encouraged to do it during the day and among friends for safety reasons.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTrick Or Treaters or Church",
        "answer": "Church.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentient machines will kill all humans because they are inferior beings.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSentient machines or all humans",
        "answer": "all humans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The dogs hate the fleas because they suck blood.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe dogs or the fleas",
        "answer": "the fleas.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy lied to his father about the crime, but he still felt uneasy and was slowly overcome with curiosity.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his father",
        "answer": "his father.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The keys typed the words because they were meant to be typed on.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe keys or the words",
        "answer": "The keys.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The criminal shocked John, because he was not expecting it.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe criminal or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary had a little lamb until she was stolen by Cindy.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or a little lamb",
        "answer": "a little lamb.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The campus police pepper sprayed the UC Davis students, so they faced an angry backlash by those who do not agree with their actions.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe campus police or the UC Davis students",
        "answer": "the UC Davis students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The committee increased the price of the tickets to the dance for the students, but they changed their decision later.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe committee or the students",
        "answer": "The committee.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve went to the meeting with John because he was asked to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy lied to his father about the crime, but he still felt uneasy and was slowly overcome with guilt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his father",
        "answer": "his father.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The violin fell off the table because someone knocked it off.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe violin or the table",
        "answer": "the table.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "South Korea does not like North Korea because they are constantly threatening their peace.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSouth Korea or North Korea",
        "answer": "North Korea.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The program deleted the reference to the data, but it did not delete it.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the data",
        "answer": "The program.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The hyenas scavenged from the lions because they had left scraps.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hyenas or the lions",
        "answer": "the lions.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael Phelps was fined by Judge Louis because he has to uphold federal law.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael Phelps or Judge Louis",
        "answer": "Judge Louis.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The general fired his pistol at the monster so he turned and looked.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe general or the monster",
        "answer": "the monster.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd traded his truck to Roger for his motorcycle since he wanted to have a truck.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLloyd or Roger",
        "answer": "Roger.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentinel tried to betray Optimus by enslaving the human race, but he did not succeed in his plan.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSentinel or Optimus",
        "answer": "Sentinel.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Tatoo artists specialize in creating works of arts on their customers, because they are paid professionals in their field.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTatoo artists or their customers",
        "answer": "their customers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some actors choose to perform their own stunts instead of using stunt doubles since they like to keep it as authentic as possible.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome actors or stunt doubles",
        "answer": "Some actors.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Home Owners Association denied the request by the Pittsburg family for a new shed since they failed to pay the annual fee.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Home Owners Association or the Pittsburg family",
        "answer": "the Pittsburg family.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Carl borrowed a book from Richard, but the book was unreadable to him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCarl or Richard",
        "answer": "Richard.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Toyota has the luxury brand Lexus: they are built for the rich.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLexus or Toyota",
        "answer": "Toyota.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bowl had a crack, so it was filled in.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bowl or a crack",
        "answer": "a crack.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mongolians attacked the Chinese because they are always eager for war.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Mongolians or the Chinese",
        "answer": "the Chinese.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The skeleton was scarier than the pumpkin, because it was rather simplistic and orange.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe skeleton or the pumpkin",
        "answer": "the pumpkin.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The CIA control intelligence gathering for the United States since they need to stay one step ahead of others to remain a superpower.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe CIA or the United States",
        "answer": "the United States.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The keys typed the words because they were meant to be typed.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe keys or the words",
        "answer": "the words.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gorden got mad at his brother because he forgot to bring him chocolate.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGorden or his brother",
        "answer": "his brother.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob kicked Larry, because he made a condescending comment.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The mother bear attacked Karen because she was worried for her cub.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe mother bear or Karen",
        "answer": "Karen.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ray William Johnson surpassed NigaHiga in Youtube subscribers, but he wants to increase the gap even more.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRay William Johnson or NigaHiga",
        "answer": "Ray William Johnson.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John shot Bill and he died.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary had a little lamb until she had lamb chops for dinner.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or a little lamb",
        "answer": "Mary.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Autobots try to stop the Decepticons since they want the world to live in peace.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Autobots or the Decepticons",
        "answer": "The Autobots.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A banana and an apple go walking, when the red one does the talking.\n\nWho is one referring to?\nA banana or an apple",
        "answer": "an apple.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Home Owners Association denied the request by the Pittsburg family for a new shed since they felt it would not be good for the community.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Home Owners Association or the Pittsburg family",
        "answer": "the Pittsburg family.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor Swift is higher in record sales over Beyonce because more people can relate to her music.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nTaylor Swift or Beyonce",
        "answer": "Taylor Swift.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat was afraid of the dog because it was timid.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the dog",
        "answer": "the dog.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The off-campus apartments were preferred to the on-campus apartments because they were more expensive.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe off-campus apartments or the on-campus apartments",
        "answer": "the on-campus apartments.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The birds ate the seeds because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe birds or the seeds",
        "answer": "The birds.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy helped his friend move because he was going to be busy all day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim was delighted to see Jack, because he brightened up his day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or Jack",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harley hides from Dyna because she is afraid of her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nHarley or Dyna",
        "answer": "Dyna.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mongolians attacked the Chinese because they are pacifists.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Mongolians or the Chinese",
        "answer": "the Chinese.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Internet Explorer believes they have less security holes than Firefox, but they conducted the tests themselves.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nInternet Explorer or Firefox",
        "answer": "Internet Explorer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Watson beat Ken at Jeopardy because he is a superior machine.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nWatson or Ken",
        "answer": "Watson.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "South Korea does not like North Korea because they are constantly threatening their peace.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSouth Korea or North Korea",
        "answer": "North Korea.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The car passed the truck because it needed to go faster.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the truck",
        "answer": "The car.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The needle punctured the skin but it failed to register pain.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe needle or the skin",
        "answer": "the skin.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "A chicken pecked at a bug and it ran away.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nA chicken or a bug",
        "answer": "a bug.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The hyenas scavenged from the lions because they were desperate.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hyenas or the lions",
        "answer": "the lions.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentient machines will kill all humans because they are inferior beings.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSentient machines or all humans",
        "answer": "all humans.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason built Rocky a robot, and he gave it to him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJason or Rocky",
        "answer": "Rocky.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John wanted George to run for President because he did not want to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or George",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The priests quoted the words of the Bible for all the suspected witches they found, since they needed to quote holy words to rid the evil.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe priests or the suspected witches",
        "answer": "the suspected witches.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some actors choose to perform their own stunts instead of using stunt doubles since they like to keep it as authentic as possible.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome actors or stunt doubles",
        "answer": "stunt doubles.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The spear easily pierced through the armor because it was too sharp.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe spear or the armor",
        "answer": "the armor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy secretly watched his friend because he had the secret information.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The prosecutor viciously attacked the defendants since they are trying to convict them of the crime.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prosecutor or the defendants",
        "answer": "The prosecutor.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student told the instructor that he talked fast.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the instructor",
        "answer": "the instructor.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John killed Bill because he was fighting for his life.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The article about the fires said that they torched most of Seattle.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe article or the fires",
        "answer": "the fires.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob sued Bill because he was embezzling funds.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill asked Joe if he could borrow some money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Joe",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain America lost a good friend, Michael, because he was killed in an accident.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain America or Michael",
        "answer": "Michael.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The program could successfully parse the file because it was formatted well.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the file",
        "answer": "the file.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The program could successfully parse the file because it was programmed well.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the file",
        "answer": "the file.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bug was flying towards the light, but it was extinguished prematurely.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bug or the light",
        "answer": "the light.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The mermaid swam toward Sue and waved her tail.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nThe mermaid or Sue",
        "answer": "The mermaid.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy lied to his father about the crime, but he still felt uneasy and was slowly overcome with guilt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his father",
        "answer": "The boy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Detroit Lions beat the Dallas Cowboys because they were unprepared.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Detroit Lions or the Dallas Cowboys",
        "answer": "the Dallas Cowboys.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Google Plus is expected to be a replacement for Facebook but it still does not have enough active users.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nGoogle Plus or Facebook",
        "answer": "Facebook.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The government revoked the ability for oil companies to drill in the United States since they are trying to drill for more oil reserves.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe government or oil companies",
        "answer": "oil companies.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The US government declared war on Iraq because they were responding to their attack on US soil.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe US government or Iraq",
        "answer": "The US government.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Billy beat Tommy at Scrabble because that newbie had all the luck.\n\nWho is that newbie referring to?\nBilly or Tommy",
        "answer": "Billy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John killed Bill because he was fighting for his life.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The skeleton was scarier than the pumpkin, because it looked like it was walking.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe skeleton or the pumpkin",
        "answer": "The skeleton.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob sued Bill because he wanted more money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe put Bob in the time machine and he created another one.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Bob",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Yuri owed Ivan money because he lost the bet.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nYuri or Ivan",
        "answer": "Yuri.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The fisherman hooked a big fish but he dropped his pole.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe fisherman or a big fish",
        "answer": "a big fish.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat was afraid of the dog because it was timid.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the dog",
        "answer": "The cat.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The people protested the government because they were raising taxes.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe people or the government",
        "answer": "the government.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A banana and an apple go walking, when the yellow one does the talking.\n\nWho is one referring to?\nA banana or an apple",
        "answer": "A banana.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The patrons enjoyed the food made by the chefs immensely because they made the food with exquisite sauces.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe patrons or the chefs",
        "answer": "the chefs.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some actors choose to perform their own stunts instead of using stunt doubles although they are professionals who specialize in stunts.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome actors or stunt doubles",
        "answer": "stunt doubles.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The plane was in the sky and it was cloudy.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe plane or the sky",
        "answer": "the sky.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tradition dictated the captain hold the Stanley Cup first, and it was pretty.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nTradition or the Stanley Cup",
        "answer": "the Stanley Cup.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Pei Wei sells sesame chicken as a signature dish since they have much demand for this particular dish.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPei Wei or sesame chicken",
        "answer": "Pei Wei.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Saudi Arabians do not respect the Bangladeshis because they are poor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSaudi Arabians or Bangladeshis",
        "answer": "Bangladeshis.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The US government declared war on Iraq because they attacked on US soil.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe US government or Iraq",
        "answer": "Iraq.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Penguins scored two goals against the Flyers in two minutes because they are more skilled.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Penguins or the Flyers",
        "answer": "The Penguins.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Californians are better than New Yorkers because they do not have Hollywood lots to produce movies.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCalifornians or New Yorkers",
        "answer": "New Yorkers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The patrons enjoyed the food made by the chefs immensely, so they paid very well to enjoy this meal.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe patrons or the chefs",
        "answer": "The patrons.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Penguins scored two goals against the Flyers in two minutes because they were not concentrating.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Penguins or the Flyers",
        "answer": "the Flyers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentinel tried to betray Optimus by enslaving the human race, but he did not succeed in his plan.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSentinel or Optimus",
        "answer": "Optimus.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rebecca kissed Dina because she is a sweet girl.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nRebecca or Dina",
        "answer": "Dina.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it flew straight at the poor animal.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "the ball.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill likes to play with Bob but he did not want to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The victims of the Black Plague blamed the witches for causing the curse because they did not understand diseases at the time.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe victims of the Black Plague or the witches",
        "answer": "the witches.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The patrons enjoyed the food made by the chefs immensely, so they paid very well to enjoy this meal.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe patrons or the chefs",
        "answer": "the chefs.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack got more votes than John because the people did not like him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nJack or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man killed the boss because he hated the job.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boss",
        "answer": "the boss.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry purchased some of Marty's Lemonade, and he wanted the recipe.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLarry or Marty",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The professor gave the student a bad grade because he was strict.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe professor or the student",
        "answer": "the student.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Raiden could not follow and guide Liu Kang in the world of darkness since he could not enter this realm without breaking the rules.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaiden or Liu Kang",
        "answer": "Liu Kang.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Disney World offers a much wider array of rides than Six Flags since they are more limited on budget due to not having other sources of revenue.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDisney World or Six Flags",
        "answer": "Six Flags.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob can beat Larry at arm wrestling because he has more muscles.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Someone hit Billy in the face because he was being rude.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSomeone or Billy",
        "answer": "Billy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve hired Jose because he could not find anyone better.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or Jose",
        "answer": "Steve.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Liverpool lost to Manchester United because they had been mismanaged all season.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLiverpool or Manchester United",
        "answer": "Manchester United.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The mother bear attacked Karen because she had gotten too close to her cub.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe mother bear or Karen",
        "answer": "Karen.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Olga kicked Sara because she woke her up.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlga or Sara",
        "answer": "Sara.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John fired Bill because he was incompetent.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer talked to the employee about firing him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nThe employer or the employee",
        "answer": "the employee.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "He likes Cuba and hates Japan because it is not a communist country.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nCuba or Japan",
        "answer": "Japan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Cats are more territorial than dogs, but they can also be territorial at times when marking their territory.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCats or dogs",
        "answer": "dogs.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The public school board of educators initiated a physical education plan on the students since they scored so low on the health and fitness standardized test.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe public school board of educators or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "George scored against Thomas in the shootout, so he lost the game.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGeorge or Thomas",
        "answer": "Thomas.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe crashed into Mike and he had to pay for the damage.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Mike",
        "answer": "Mike.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice beat Texas, even though they were a smaller school.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRice or Texas",
        "answer": "Texas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Californians are better than New Yorkers because they have Hollywood.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCalifornians or New Yorkers",
        "answer": "New Yorkers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "I gave the donkey some food because it was fresh.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nsome food or the donkey",
        "answer": "some food.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain Picard tends to confide in Commander Riker because he needs to soak up as much experience as he can.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain Picard or Commander Riker",
        "answer": "Commander Riker.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Olivia wants to make amends with Emily, but she is apprehensive.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlivia or Emily",
        "answer": "Olivia.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A banana and an apple go walking, when the yellow one does the talking.\n\nWho is one referring to?\nA banana or an apple",
        "answer": "an apple.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Range Rover recently revealed their new lineup of cars at Times Square for thousands of New Yorkers since they are advertising their new high end models.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRange Rover or thousands of New Yorkers",
        "answer": "Range Rover.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary gave Sandy her book because she is generous.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Sandy",
        "answer": "Mary.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The pen is mightier than the sword because it can be used to write world-changing documents.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe pen or the sword",
        "answer": "The pen.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelly neglected to tell Katie that their rent was due, but she remembered that it was due on the first of every month.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nKelly or Katie",
        "answer": "Katie.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The geology department petitioned the school board for money because they needed funding.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe geology department or the school board",
        "answer": "The geology department.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Federer consistently beat Nadal since he was the better tennis player.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFederer or Nadal",
        "answer": "Federer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Autobots try to stop the Decepticons since they want the world to live in peace.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Autobots or the Decepticons",
        "answer": "the Decepticons.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Intel Performs better than AMD in the processing market, but they are more successful in the graphics market instead.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nIntel or AMD",
        "answer": "AMD.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The car passed the truck because it needed to go faster.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the truck",
        "answer": "the truck.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Research studies recently revealed that Netflix consumes over 37 percent of the world's internet bandwidth since they need that much due to high demand of their streaming services.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nResearch studies or Netflix",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The article about the fires said that they torched most of Seattle.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe article or the fires",
        "answer": "the fires.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Richard blackmailed Senator Carson so that his rise to power would be secured.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nRichard or Senator Carson",
        "answer": "Senator Carson.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The car beat the bike because it was too slow.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the bike",
        "answer": "the bike.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John killed Bill because he was a zombie.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Marines are considerably afraid of the aliens, but they will still use their discipline to overcome their fears.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Marines or the aliens",
        "answer": "The Marines.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Carl borrowed a book from Richard, but the book was unreadable to him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCarl or Richard",
        "answer": "Carl.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Penguins scored two goals against the Flyers in two minutes because they are more skilled.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Penguins or the Flyers",
        "answer": "the Flyers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The blacksmith refused to repair the armor for the knight because he did not have any money to pay with.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe blacksmith or the knight",
        "answer": "the knight.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy secretly watched his friend because he wanted the secret information.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain Picard tends to confide in Commander Riker because he needs to soak up as much experience as he can.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain Picard or Commander Riker",
        "answer": "Commander Riker.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The leech latched onto the hippo because it was hungry.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe leech or the hippo",
        "answer": "the hippo.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael decided to freeze himself in cryo-stasis even though his father was against it, so he tried to convince him not to do it.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael or his father",
        "answer": "his father.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The humans were afraid of the robots because they were strong.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe humans or the robots",
        "answer": "the robots.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Data is an android who can learn new materials much faster than Acting Ensign Wesley since he has the ability to learn vasts amount of information quickly into his database.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nData or Acting Ensign Wesley",
        "answer": "Data.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The football players went on strike against the NFL organization, but they will consider their demands to send the strike.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe football players or the NFL organization",
        "answer": "the NFL organization.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The minister befriended King George so he could have some friends.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe minister or King George",
        "answer": "King George.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Cats are more territorial than dogs since they always try and insert their dominance over others.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCats or dogs",
        "answer": "Cats.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Playstation is outperforming the Xbox because it has better games.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Playstation or the Xbox",
        "answer": "The Playstation.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The clown smiled at the child and he cried.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe clown or the child",
        "answer": "the child.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The spear easily pierced through the armor because it was too sharp.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe spear or the armor",
        "answer": "The spear.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Canada is bigger than the United Kingdom, but they have a much larger population.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCanada or the United Kingdom",
        "answer": "the United Kingdom.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "A chicken pecked at a bug and it ate it.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nA chicken or a bug",
        "answer": "a bug.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Adam failed to kill Alexander, so he hired an assassin for the second attempt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nAdam or Alexander",
        "answer": "Alexander.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The leech latched onto the hippo because it was hungry.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe leech or the hippo",
        "answer": "The leech.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Pigs are better than sheep because they make bacon.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPigs or sheep",
        "answer": "sheep.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The FDA revoked the medical licenses of corrupt doctors since they enforce strict medical guidelines.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe FDA or corrupt doctors",
        "answer": "corrupt doctors.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Olivia wants to make amends with Emily, but she no longer wants to be friends.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlivia or Emily",
        "answer": "Emily.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rebecca kissed Dina because she loves her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nRebecca or Dina",
        "answer": "Dina.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger cannot terminate John Conner, because he is the leader of the resistance.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nArnold Schwarzenegger or John Conner",
        "answer": "John Conner.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleece feels better than cotton since they are of worse quality.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFleece or cotton",
        "answer": "cotton.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Guns generally increase in value over time to gun collectors if unfired, because they need to be in mint condition to be extremely valuable.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGuns or gun collectors",
        "answer": "Guns.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The SWAT team moved in on the compound to prevent the terrorists from launching a deadly missile because they wanted to preserve the lives of innocents.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe SWAT team or the terrorists",
        "answer": "The SWAT team.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The gym teachers trained the students because they wanted to become better players.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe gym teachers or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Walking Dead is proving to be a big hit among zombie enthusiasts because they have made a series that greatly appeals to them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Walking Dead or zombie enthusiasts",
        "answer": "The Walking Dead.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill asked Joe if he could borrow some money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Joe",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The salesperson told Dave that this would be the best car he ever sold.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe salesperson or Dave",
        "answer": "The salesperson.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ken tried to sneak past the boss because he was looking for late people.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKen or the boss",
        "answer": "the boss.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Saudi Arabians do not respect the Bangladeshis because they are rich.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSaudi Arabians or Bangladeshis",
        "answer": "Bangladeshis.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob can beat Larry at arm wrestling because he is a toddler.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe raced against Steven because he thought it would be easy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Steven",
        "answer": "Steven.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The gym teachers trained the students because they wanted to teach them discipline.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe gym teachers or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Harvey Dent blames the Batman for losing his love because he was saved instead of his girlfriend.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHarvey Dent or the Batman",
        "answer": "the Batman.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelson punched Milhouse but he was not hurt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNelson or Milhouse",
        "answer": "Milhouse.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary smiled at Susan, but she was not happy to see her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Susan",
        "answer": "Mary.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John rated Bill because he was a contestant.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary likes Joe because she has a cool name.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Joe",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Schrodinger's cat walks into an empty building, but does it contain him?\n\nWho is it referring to?\nSchrodinger's cat or an empty building",
        "answer": "an empty building.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My heart pumps blood because it is a muscle.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy heart or blood",
        "answer": "blood.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Gorden got mad at his brother because he did not get good sleep.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGorden or his brother",
        "answer": "Gorden.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ghost entered the house because it was haunting.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe ghost or the house",
        "answer": "The ghost.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe smells better than Adam since he hardly ever showers.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "George scored against Thomas in the shootout, so he won the game.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGeorge or Thomas",
        "answer": "George.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Liverpool lost to Manchester United because they had been mismanaged all season.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLiverpool or Manchester United",
        "answer": "Liverpool.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob kicked Larry, because he was mad.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man killed the boss because he hated the job.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boss",
        "answer": "The man.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Liverpool lost to Manchester United because they were a superior team.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLiverpool or Manchester United",
        "answer": "Manchester United.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The racquetball players were annoyed by the other students in the activity center because they were using the racquetball courts to play badminton.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe racquetball players or the other students",
        "answer": "the other students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it was designed to be hit.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "the ball.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Parents care for their children considerably because they love them undeniably to want to keep them save.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nParents or their children",
        "answer": "Parents.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox News is more popular in ratings than CNN since they are more interesting.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFox News or CNN",
        "answer": "CNN.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The paintball player was mad at the referee because he missed a call.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe paintball player or the referee",
        "answer": "the referee.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mom brought Sara from school early because she had an early meeting.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMom or Sara",
        "answer": "Mom.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Speed boats need to pass strict tests for use while row boats have no guidelines because they are powered by paddles instead of mechanical engines.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSpeed boats or row boats",
        "answer": "row boats.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Steven Seagal challenged Jean Claude Van Damme to a fight because he is a worthy opponent.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteven Seagal or Jean Claude Van Damme",
        "answer": "Jean Claude Van Damme.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The state executes prisoners because they want justice.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe state or prisoners",
        "answer": "The state.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The U.S.S Enterprise tried to assist a sister ship, but they arrived too late to save them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe U.S.S Enterprise or a sister ship",
        "answer": "a sister ship.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The SWAT team moved in on the compound to prevent the terrorists from launching a deadly missile because they wanted to preserve the lives of innocents.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe SWAT team or the terrorists",
        "answer": "the terrorists.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Francis stopped and looked at the penguin because he was cute.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFrancis or the penguin",
        "answer": "the penguin.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The priests quoted the words of the Bible for all the suspected witches they found, since they feared the words of the Bible.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe priests or the suspected witches",
        "answer": "the suspected witches.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Apple was in talks with Verizon to be their dedicated phone provider initially because they were a prime candidate to provide their service.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nApple or Verizon",
        "answer": "Verizon.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Francis stopped and looked at the penguin because he was intrigued.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFrancis or the penguin",
        "answer": "Francis.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "AMD recently managed to break a record in the New Guiness Book of Records, because they managed to overclock their processor to unheard heights.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAMD or the New Guiness Book of Records",
        "answer": "AMD.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John called Bill because he was a good listener.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Intel performs better than AMD in the processing market, but they do not do as well in the graphics market.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nIntel or AMD",
        "answer": "AMD.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Saudi Arabians do not respect the Bangladeshis because they are rich.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSaudi Arabians or Bangladeshis",
        "answer": "Saudi Arabians.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph did not defeat William in the match, so he earned $100.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoseph or William",
        "answer": "William.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean is better than Watson at anaphora resolution because he can naturally understand natural language.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSean or Watson",
        "answer": "Watson.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Dell replaced all their Blackberry phones with their own because they lost confidence in their brand due to to recent network outage.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDell or their Blackberry phones",
        "answer": "Dell.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe smells better than Adam since he showers regularly.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The CIA control intelligence gathering for the United States because they have some of the best people who specialize in this type of work.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe CIA or the United States",
        "answer": "The CIA.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The criminal shocked John, because he was not expecting it.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe criminal or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The SWAT team moved in on the compound to prevent the terrorists from launching a deadly missile because they were trying to terrorize the global population.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe SWAT team or the terrorists",
        "answer": "the terrorists.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The birds ate the seeds because they were tasty.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe birds or the seeds",
        "answer": "the seeds.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "He likes Cuba and hates Japan because it is a communist country.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nCuba or Japan",
        "answer": "Japan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The network heads cancelled the TV shows because they did not like the content.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe network heads or the TV shows",
        "answer": "The network heads.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The clown smiled at the child and he offered him a balloon.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe clown or the child",
        "answer": "The clown.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jupiter is bigger than the Earth, but it is lighter due to being mostly gas.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nJupiter or the Earth",
        "answer": "Jupiter.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat was afraid of the dog because it was scary.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the dog",
        "answer": "the dog.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Josie did not like Sarah, but she did not tell her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJosie or Sarah",
        "answer": "Sarah.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The leech latched onto the hippo so that it could enjoy the sunshine.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe leech or the hippo",
        "answer": "the hippo.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The FDA revoked the medical licenses of corrupt doctors because they have been improperly issuing drugs.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe FDA or corrupt doctors",
        "answer": "corrupt doctors.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy escaped the cop but he continued to flee.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or the cop",
        "answer": "The boy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Rick Perry is doing stronger than Mitt Romney in the polls, but he is coming back as a strong candidate.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRick Perry or Mitt Romney",
        "answer": "Mitt Romney.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The sniper shot the terrorist because he had orders.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe sniper or the terrorist",
        "answer": "The sniper.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Autobots try to stop the Decepticons since they want to destroy the world.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Autobots or the Decepticons",
        "answer": "the Decepticons.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelson punched Milhouse but he was not hurt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNelson or Milhouse",
        "answer": "Milhouse.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "JP Morgan Bank developed a mobile banking application which gives an edge over competitor Bank of America, but they will probably develop their own mobile application soon as well.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nJP Morgan Bank or Bank of America",
        "answer": "Bank of America.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy helped his friend move because he was going to be busy all day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The public school board of educators initiated a physical education plan on the students so that they could help them become healthy again.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe public school board of educators or the students",
        "answer": "The public school board of educators.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Nola shot Christina in the head because she threatened to take all of her money.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nNola or Christina",
        "answer": "Christina.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The U.S.S Enterprise tried to assist a sister ship, but they arrived too late to save them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe U.S.S Enterprise or a sister ship",
        "answer": "The U.S.S Enterprise.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mad Hatter tried to offer a cup of tea to the March Hare, but his hat was too distracting.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nThe Mad Hatter or the March Hare",
        "answer": "the March Hare.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Someone hit Billy in the face because he was angry.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSomeone or Billy",
        "answer": "Billy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it flew in the way of the trajectory.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "The bat.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The criminal shocked John, because he pulled out a gun.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe criminal or John",
        "answer": "The criminal.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Playstation is outperforming the Xbox because it is prone to hardware failure.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Playstation or the Xbox",
        "answer": "the Xbox.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor Swift is higher in record sales over Beyonce because people are not passionate about her music.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nTaylor Swift or Beyonce",
        "answer": "Beyonce.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Watson beat Ken at Jeopardy because he is an inferior human.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nWatson or Ken",
        "answer": "Ken.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campus police pepper sprayed the UC Davis students, so they faced an angry backlash by those who do not agree with their actions.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe campus police or the UC Davis students",
        "answer": "The campus police.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The professor gave the student a bad grade because he was strict.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe professor or the student",
        "answer": "The professor.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The apple wine entered my mouth because it tastes good.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe apple wine or my mouth",
        "answer": "The apple wine.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Two deserted crusaders agreed to transport a girl for the priests, but they agreed in exchange for being pardoned.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTwo deserted crusaders or the priests",
        "answer": "Two deserted crusaders.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man shot his friend and he was arrested.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleece feels better than cotton since they are much softer.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFleece or cotton",
        "answer": "Fleece.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Pei Wei sells sesame chicken as a signature dish, so they are constantly picked as an order.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPei Wei or sesame chicken",
        "answer": "sesame chicken.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry trusted Page because Bill knows him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nLarry or Page",
        "answer": "Page.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark tried to sabotage Tom, but he got caught in the process.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMark or Tom",
        "answer": "Tom.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bowl had a crack, so it was thrown away.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bowl or a crack",
        "answer": "The bowl.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The off-campus apartments were preferred to the on-campus apartments because they were more expensive.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe off-campus apartments or the on-campus apartments",
        "answer": "the on-campus apartments.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Dallas Cowboys are more successful as a franchise than the Saints because they are considered \"America's Team\".\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Dallas Cowboys or the Saints",
        "answer": "The Dallas Cowboys.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man offered the boy candy, but he had no candy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boy",
        "answer": "the boy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The network heads cancelled the TV shows because they were not doing well.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe network heads or the TV shows",
        "answer": "the TV shows.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "President Clinton pardoned Roger Clinton because he was the president's half-brother.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPresident Clinton or Roger Clinton",
        "answer": "Roger Clinton.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Canada is bigger than the United Kingdom, but they do not have the population to back it up.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCanada or the United Kingdom",
        "answer": "Canada.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lois was scolded by her daughter because she was accused of being a terrible mother.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLois or her daughter",
        "answer": "Lois.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "I gave the donkey some food because it was fresh.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nsome food or the donkey",
        "answer": "the donkey.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Banks usually offer bonus points for new credit card applicants because they are often enticed by free offerings.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBanks or new credit card applicants",
        "answer": "new credit card applicants.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe put Bob in the time machine and he went to the future.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Data is an android who can learn new materials much faster than Acting Ensign Wesley, because he does not have an electronic brain to learn as quickly.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nData or Acting Ensign Wesley",
        "answer": "Acting Ensign Wesley.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy secretly watched his friend because he wanted the secret information.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "The boy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Internet Explorer believes they have less security holes than Firefox, but they do not trust Microsoft's test results.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nInternet Explorer or Firefox",
        "answer": "Firefox.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The winners were given the awards after they were made.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe winners or the awards",
        "answer": "the awards.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The baby cow cried at the farmer because he had milk.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe baby cow or the farmer",
        "answer": "the farmer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelly neglected to tell Katie that their rent was due, but she told her later.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nKelly or Katie",
        "answer": "Katie.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mel got in trouble with a collector named Bohr because he lost a huge sum of money due to his gambling habit.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMel or a collector named Bohr",
        "answer": "Mel.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jill saw Jane fall down, and she helped her up.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJill or Jane",
        "answer": "Jill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd traded his truck to Roger for his motorcycle since he wanted to have a truck.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLloyd or Roger",
        "answer": "Roger.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald Trump fired his servant, Luigi, but he can find another job elsewhere.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald Trump or Luigi",
        "answer": "Luigi.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The ghost entered the house because it was haunting.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe ghost or the house",
        "answer": "the house.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Nola shot Christina in the head because she threatened to take all of her money.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nNola or Christina",
        "answer": "Christina.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some fan girls created a rap about Windows phones because they are in love with their new electronics.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome fan girls or Windows phones",
        "answer": "Windows phones.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The keys typed the words because they were meant to be typed.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe keys or the words",
        "answer": "the words.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "My phone is working better than your phone because it is broken.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy phone or your phone",
        "answer": "your phone.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Battlefield 3 is more fun than Modern Warfare 3 because it is a crappy game.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nBattlefield 3 or Modern Warfare 3",
        "answer": "Modern Warfare 3.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The prisoners were held captive by the German forces since they needed to gather intelligence from them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prisoners or the German forces",
        "answer": "the German forces.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Detroit Lions beat the Dallas Cowboys because they were unprepared.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Detroit Lions or the Dallas Cowboys",
        "answer": "the Dallas Cowboys.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The off-campus apartments were preferred to the on-campus apartments because they were cheaper.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe off-campus apartments or the on-campus apartments",
        "answer": "the on-campus apartments.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob asked Tom if he could take him to the movies.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Tom",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Some enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers are already lining up at retail stores because they have some really low priced items that will be on sale.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers or retail stores",
        "answer": "retail stores.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John introduced Bill because he was new.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Some Motorcycle enthusiasts are selling a TRON lightcycle to TRON fans, but they may be turned off by the asking price.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome Motorcycle enthusiasts or TRON fans",
        "answer": "TRON fans.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "JP Morgan Bank developed a mobile banking application which gives an edge over competitor Bank of America, but they will probably develop their own mobile application soon as well.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nJP Morgan Bank or Bank of America",
        "answer": "Bank of America.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Gates is similar to Steve Jobs, but he is the previous CEO of Microsoft.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Gates or Steve Jobs",
        "answer": "Bill Gates.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mongolians attacked the Chinese because they are pacifists.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Mongolians or the Chinese",
        "answer": "the Chinese.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The geology department petitioned the school board for money because they could grant funding.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe geology department or the school board",
        "answer": "the school board.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The baby cow cried at the farmer because he wanted milk.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe baby cow or the farmer",
        "answer": "the farmer.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleece feels better than cotton since they are much softer.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFleece or cotton",
        "answer": "cotton.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The light hit the mirror and it shattered.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe light or the mirror",
        "answer": "the mirror.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Canada is bigger than the United Kingdom, but they have a much larger population.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCanada or the United Kingdom",
        "answer": "the United Kingdom.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The knife sliced through the flesh because it was sharp.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe knife or the flesh",
        "answer": "the flesh.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Schrodinger's cat walks into an empty building, but where is it now?\n\nWho is it referring to?\nSchrodinger's cat or an empty building",
        "answer": "Schrodinger's cat.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My phone is working better than your phone because it is broken.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy phone or your phone",
        "answer": "your phone.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mom brought Sara from school early because she was sick.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMom or Sara",
        "answer": "Sara.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Guns generally increase in value over time to gun collectors if unfired, because they need to be in mint condition to be extremely valuable.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGuns or gun collectors",
        "answer": "gun collectors.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sheila tried to repair the old jalopy, even though she had not worked on cars in three decades.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nSheila or the old jalopy",
        "answer": "Sheila.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John visited Luke in the hospital because he was sick.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Luke",
        "answer": "Luke.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The pen is mightier than the sword because it can only stab things.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe pen or the sword",
        "answer": "the sword.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mel got in trouble with a collector named Bohr because he lost a huge sum of money due to his gambling habit.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMel or a collector named Bohr",
        "answer": "a collector named Bohr.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tony helped Jeff because he needed help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nTony or Jeff",
        "answer": "Jeff.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jill saw Jane fall down, and she asked her for help.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJill or Jane",
        "answer": "Jane.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sheila tried to repair the old jalopy, even though she had not run in three decades.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nSheila or the old jalopy",
        "answer": "the old jalopy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The CIA control intelligence gathering for the United States because they have some of the best people who specialize in this type of work.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe CIA or the United States",
        "answer": "the United States.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bug was flying towards the light, but it was exterminated prematurely.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bug or the light",
        "answer": "the light.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlet powered the lamp when it had electricity.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe outlet or the lamp",
        "answer": "the lamp.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Skyline drifts better than the F-150 because it is not meant to drift.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Skyline or the F-150",
        "answer": "the F-150.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The security team locked the scientists inside the building because they had to keep confidential information inside.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe security team or the scientists",
        "answer": "The security team.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Some Motorcycle enthusiasts are selling a TRON lightcycle to TRON fans because they specialize in making movie related vehicles.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome Motorcycle enthusiasts or TRON fans",
        "answer": "TRON fans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Data is an android who can learn new materials much faster than Acting Ensign Wesley, because he does not have an electronic brain to learn as quickly.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nData or Acting Ensign Wesley",
        "answer": "Acting Ensign Wesley.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentinel tried to betray Optimus by enslaving the human race because he wanted the humans to rule again.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSentinel or Optimus",
        "answer": "Optimus.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The car passed the truck because it was going too slow.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the truck",
        "answer": "the truck.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The hotel staff tended to the royal family since they needed to keep them satisfied as occupants.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hotel staff or the royal family",
        "answer": "The hotel staff.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The government revoked the ability for oil companies to drill in the United States since they are trying to drill for more oil reserves.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe government or oil companies",
        "answer": "oil companies.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Next Generation was well received by Trekkies, but they will always perceive the first Star Trek to be the best.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Next Generation or Trekkies",
        "answer": "Trekkies.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob can beat Larry at arm wrestling because he is a toddler.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man offered the boy candy, but he got no candy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boy",
        "answer": "the boy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it flew straight at the poor animal.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "the ball.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bug was flying towards the light, but it was exterminated prematurely.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bug or the light",
        "answer": "The bug.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it was designed to be hit.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "the ball.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The program could successfully parse the file because it was formatted well.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the file",
        "answer": "the file.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The general fired his pistol at the monster so he could be a distraction.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe general or the monster",
        "answer": "the monster.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The racquetball players were annoyed by the other students in the activity center because they wanted to play and couldn't.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe racquetball players or the other students",
        "answer": "The racquetball players.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Military Police threw the army recruits in the brig since they were causing a distrubance in the neighboring town.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Military Police or the army recruits",
        "answer": "the army recruits.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill punched Bob in the face because he wanted to protect Mary.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The scientists gave the chimps some bananas because they were ripe.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe chimps or some bananas",
        "answer": "some bananas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The minister befriended King George so he would not get beheaded.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe minister or King George",
        "answer": "The minister.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John shot Bill and he was jailed.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "My phone is working better than your phone because it is a newer model.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy phone or your phone",
        "answer": "your phone.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Samurais respected honor while pirates have a disregard for honor, because they hold true to the policy of fighting with honor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Samurais or pirates",
        "answer": "The Samurais.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The blacksmith refused to repair the armor for the knight because he did not have any money to pay with.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe blacksmith or the knight",
        "answer": "the knight.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack got more votes than John because the people liked him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nJack or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John rated Bill because he was the judge.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentinel tried to betray Optimus by enslaving the human race because he wanted the humans to rule again.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSentinel or Optimus",
        "answer": "Optimus.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The light hit the mirror and it shattered.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe light or the mirror",
        "answer": "the mirror.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Planet 343's sandstorm forces the inhabitants underground, but they have plenty of food sources stored away.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPlanet 343's sandstorm or the inhabitants",
        "answer": "the inhabitants.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Military Police threw the army recruits in the brig since they were enforcing the rules of being in the army.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Military Police or the army recruits",
        "answer": "The Military Police.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The management provided bonuses to the employees since they wanted to keep their workers happy at the company.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe management or the employees",
        "answer": "the employees.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "He likes Cuba and hates Japan because it is not a communist country.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nCuba or Japan",
        "answer": "Japan.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Eagles managed to completely dominate the Cowboys this weekend, but they were able to at least keep it from being a shutout.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Eagles or the Cowboys",
        "answer": "the Cowboys.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Christian Bale once lost his temper at the man holding his lighting, but he did not do anything that earned getting yelled at.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nChristian Bale or the man",
        "answer": "the man.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Liverpool lost to Manchester United because they were a superior team.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLiverpool or Manchester United",
        "answer": "Manchester United.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lois was scolded by her daughter because she was accused of being a terrible mother.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLois or her daughter",
        "answer": "her daughter.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger cannot terminate John Conner, because he is protecting him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nArnold Schwarzenegger or John Conner",
        "answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Some fan girls created a rap about Windows phones because they are in love with their new electronics.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome fan girls or Windows phones",
        "answer": "Some fan girls.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gamers are generally perceived as nerds compared to athletes since they are stereotypically social and in good shape.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGamers or athletes",
        "answer": "athletes.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bowl had a crack, so it was thrown away.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bowl or a crack",
        "answer": "a crack.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "South Korea does not like North Korea because they are always forced to defend their peace.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSouth Korea or North Korea",
        "answer": "South Korea.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The hotel staff tended to the royal family, however, they felt the service was unsatisfactory.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hotel staff or the royal family",
        "answer": "the royal family.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The city council granted a permit to the construction workers because they were elected to encourage business.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe city council or the construction workers",
        "answer": "The city council.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We took the books to the shops because they were old.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe books or the shops",
        "answer": "the shops.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor Swift is higher in record sales over Beyonce because people are not passionate about her music.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nTaylor Swift or Beyonce",
        "answer": "Beyonce.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cats attacked the humans because they were feral.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe cats or the humans",
        "answer": "the humans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "We gave the fruit to the humans because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe fruit or the humans",
        "answer": "the humans.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campers turned on their flashlights because it was dark without them.\n\nWho is them referring to?\nThe campers or their flashlights",
        "answer": "their flashlights.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The off-campus apartments were preferred to the on-campus apartments because they were cheaper.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe off-campus apartments or the on-campus apartments",
        "answer": "The off-campus apartments.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Scientists have created a serum which transforms men into super soldiers, but they may experience side effects.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nScientists or men",
        "answer": "men.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jill saw Jane fall down, and she asked her for help.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJill or Jane",
        "answer": "Jane.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The blimp hit the tree because it was in the way.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe blimp or the tree",
        "answer": "the tree.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cheetah outran the antelope so it got to eat.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cheetah or the antelope",
        "answer": "The cheetah.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Military Police threw the army recruits in the brig since they were enforcing the rules of being in the army.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Military Police or the army recruits",
        "answer": "the army recruits.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob sued Bill because he wanted more money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Bill",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The people protested the government because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe people or the government",
        "answer": "The people.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Raja wanted Rena to take the job because he would be a good candidate.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaja or Rena",
        "answer": "Rena.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John visited Luke in the hospital because he lived close by.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Luke",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ray William Johnson surpassed NigaHiga in Youtube subscribers, but he considers that being number two is still a huge achievement.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRay William Johnson or NigaHiga",
        "answer": "NigaHiga.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The football players went on strike against the NFL organization, but they will consider their demands to send the strike.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe football players or the NFL organization",
        "answer": "the NFL organization.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The car beat the bike because it was faster.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the bike",
        "answer": "the bike.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The FDA revoked the medical licenses of corrupt doctors since they enforce strict medical guidelines.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe FDA or corrupt doctors",
        "answer": "The FDA.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain America lost a good friend, Michael, because he could not catch him before falling.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain America or Michael",
        "answer": "Captain America.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "AMD recently managed to break a record in the New Guiness Book of Records, so they immortalized them in their record keeping.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAMD or the New Guiness Book of Records",
        "answer": "the New Guiness Book of Records.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The salesperson told Dave that this would be the best car he ever bought.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe salesperson or Dave",
        "answer": "Dave.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campus police pepper sprayed the UC Davis students because they were blocking private property.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe campus police or the UC Davis students",
        "answer": "the UC Davis students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Kung Fu teachers try to pass on discipline to their disciples since they want them to learn more than just technique.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nKung Fu teachers or their disciples",
        "answer": "their disciples.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlaw shot the sheriff, but he did not shoot the deputy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe outlaw or the sheriff",
        "answer": "the sheriff.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Adam failed to kill Alexander, so he hired a bodygaurd in case of a second attempt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nAdam or Alexander",
        "answer": "Alexander.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Francis stopped and looked at the penguin because he was cute.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFrancis or the penguin",
        "answer": "the penguin.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael Phelps was fined by Judge Louis because he was caught with illegal drugs.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael Phelps or Judge Louis",
        "answer": "Michael Phelps.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The racquetball players were annoyed by the other students in the activity center because they wanted to play and couldn't.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe racquetball players or the other students",
        "answer": "the other students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Detroit Lions beat the Dallas Cowboys because they had more desire to win.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Detroit Lions or the Dallas Cowboys",
        "answer": "The Detroit Lions.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The humans were afraid of the robots because they were weak.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe humans or the robots",
        "answer": "The humans.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Steven Seagal challenged Jean Claude Van Damme to a fight because he is a worthy opponent.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteven Seagal or Jean Claude Van Damme",
        "answer": "Jean Claude Van Damme.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Batman constantly tried to arrest the Joker, but he always manages to get out.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBatman or the Joker",
        "answer": "the Joker.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Russian Syndicate decided to remove some of their lower members because they knew too much about their operations.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Russian Syndicate or their lower members",
        "answer": "their lower members.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe smells better than Adam since he hardly ever showers.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "King James eagerly awaited the arrival of Prince Henry so he prepared many celebrations to welcome him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKing James or Prince Henry",
        "answer": "Prince Henry.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The minister befriended King George so he would not get beheaded.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe minister or King George",
        "answer": "King George.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Speed boats need to pass strict tests for use while row boats have no guidelines because they are powered by paddles instead of mechanical engines.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSpeed boats or row boats",
        "answer": "row boats.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Guns generally increase in value over time to gun collectors if unfired, since they prefer to collect things that are in perfect condition.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGuns or gun collectors",
        "answer": "gun collectors.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Girls like puppies because they like adorable things.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGirls or puppies",
        "answer": "Girls.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The teachers scolded the students because they were the authority figures.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teachers or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill likes to play with Bob because he loves playing.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man killed the boss because he fired him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boss",
        "answer": "the boss.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The humans were afraid of the robots because they were weak.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe humans or the robots",
        "answer": "the robots.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The alter boy assisted Knight Mordron in his mission because he hopes he will get knighted afterwards.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe alter boy or Knight Mordron",
        "answer": "The alter boy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob asked Tom if he could lend some money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Tom",
        "answer": "Tom.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The slaves were forced to do the bidding of the nobles so they do not have to do any of the hard labor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe slaves or the nobles",
        "answer": "the nobles.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark tried to sabotage Tom because he wants to be employee of the month.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMark or Tom",
        "answer": "Tom.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tradition dictated the captain hold the Stanley Cup first, and it is always followed.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nTradition or the Stanley Cup",
        "answer": "Tradition.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "James Cameron is more successful than Michael Bay because his movies sell more worldwide.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nJames Cameron or Michael Bay",
        "answer": "James Cameron.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob can beat Larry at arm wrestling because he has more muscles.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some Motorcycle enthusiasts are selling a TRON lightcycle to TRON fans because they specialize in making movie related vehicles.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome Motorcycle enthusiasts or TRON fans",
        "answer": "Some Motorcycle enthusiasts.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lily gave Amber a hug because she was sad.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLily or Amber",
        "answer": "Amber.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Range Rover recently revealed their new lineup of cars at Times Square for thousands of New Yorkers so they would be enticed to purchase their cars.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRange Rover or thousands of New Yorkers",
        "answer": "thousands of New Yorkers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The chimpanzee could not use Linux because it uses different commands than Windows.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe chimpanzee or Linux",
        "answer": "Linux.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gamers are generally perceived as nerds compared to athletes since they are stereotypically anti-social.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGamers or athletes",
        "answer": "Gamers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The baby cow cried at the farmer because he had milk.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe baby cow or the farmer",
        "answer": "the farmer.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Battlefield 3 is more fun than Modern Warfare 3 because it is a better game.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nBattlefield 3 or Modern Warfare 3",
        "answer": "Modern Warfare 3.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John rated Bill because he was the judge.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jupiter is bigger than the Earth, but it is heavier due to being solid.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nJupiter or the Earth",
        "answer": "the Earth.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The CIA control intelligence gathering for the United States since they need to stay one step ahead of others to remain a superpower.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe CIA or the United States",
        "answer": "the United States.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Speed boats need to pass strict tests for use while row boats have no guidelines, since they are more prone to mechanical failures due to their moving parts.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSpeed boats or row boats",
        "answer": "row boats.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Canada is bigger than the United Kingdom, but they do not have the population to back it up.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCanada or the United Kingdom",
        "answer": "the United Kingdom.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The drug cartel enlists the help of the local population to work their fields since they are considered cheap labor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe drug cartel or the local population",
        "answer": "the local population.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The dogs hate the fleas because they hate bugs.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe dogs or the fleas",
        "answer": "the fleas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The lion saw the fish and it was swimming.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe lion or the fish",
        "answer": "the fish.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The teaching staff wanted to treat the students to a special lunch because they did so well on their standardized tests.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teaching staff or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy escaped the cop but he continued to search.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or the cop",
        "answer": "the cop.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The humans were afraid of the robots because they were strong.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe humans or the robots",
        "answer": "the robots.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jace loves Jesus because he died for him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJace or Jesus",
        "answer": "Jesus.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Audrey Hepburn made more movies than Katherine Hepburn because she was not as good at acting.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAudrey Hepburn or Katherine Hepburn",
        "answer": "Katherine Hepburn.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lily gave Amber a hug because she was sad.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLily or Amber",
        "answer": "Amber.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some actors choose to perform their own stunts instead of using stunt doubles although they are professionals who specialize in stunts.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome actors or stunt doubles",
        "answer": "stunt doubles.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Olivia wants to make amends with Emily, but she is apprehensive.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlivia or Emily",
        "answer": "Emily.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Girls like puppies because they like adorable things.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGirls or puppies",
        "answer": "puppies.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary gave Sandy her book because she needed it.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Sandy",
        "answer": "Sandy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The fisherman hooked a big fish but he dropped his pole.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe fisherman or a big fish",
        "answer": "The fisherman.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox News is more popular in ratings than CNN since they are boring.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFox News or CNN",
        "answer": "CNN.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gorden got mad at his brother because he forgot to bring him chocolate.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGorden or his brother",
        "answer": "his brother.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Toyota has the luxury brand Lexus, although they typically sell for the average consumer.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLexus or Toyota",
        "answer": "Toyota.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The board of directors reviewed the findings of the scientists to determine funding because they are interested in the potential profits for the company.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe board of directors or the scientists",
        "answer": "The board of directors.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The program deleted the reference to the data, but it did not delete it.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the data",
        "answer": "the data.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tradition dictated the captain hold the Stanley Cup first, and it is always followed.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nTradition or the Stanley Cup",
        "answer": "the Stanley Cup.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain America lost a good friend, Michael, because he could not catch him before falling.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain America or Michael",
        "answer": "Michael.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it flew in the way of the trajectory.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "the ball.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ken tried to sneak past the boss because he was looking for late people.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKen or the boss",
        "answer": "the boss.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The baby cow cried at the farmer because he wanted milk.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe baby cow or the farmer",
        "answer": "The baby cow.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox News is more popular in ratings than CNN since they are more interesting.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFox News or CNN",
        "answer": "Fox News.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ghost entered the house because it was haunted.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe ghost or the house",
        "answer": "the house.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary smiled at Susan, but she did not smile back.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Susan",
        "answer": "Susan.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Kung Fu teachers try to pass on discipline to their disciples, but they do not always learn what they are being taught very well.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nKung Fu teachers or their disciples",
        "answer": "their disciples.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "My teacher asked a student to make sentences because he wanted to see him write.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMy teacher or a student",
        "answer": "My teacher.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Scientists have created a serum which transforms men into super soldiers, because they needed to create an unstoppable army.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nScientists or men",
        "answer": "men.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve hired Jose because he could not find anyone better.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or Jose",
        "answer": "Jose.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The drug cartel enlists the help of the local population to work their fields since they need cheap labor to maximize their profits.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe drug cartel or the local population",
        "answer": "the local population.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tony helped Jeff because he needed help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nTony or Jeff",
        "answer": "Jeff.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mel got in trouble with a collector named Bohr, so he tracked him down to try to collect all the owed money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMel or a collector named Bohr",
        "answer": "a collector named Bohr.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Penguins scored two goals against the Flyers in two minutes because they were not concentrating.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Penguins or the Flyers",
        "answer": "the Flyers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Christian Bale once lost his temper at the man holding his lighting because he has a short temper.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nChristian Bale or the man",
        "answer": "Christian Bale.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Google Plus is expected to be a replacement for Facebook but it still has a lot more active users.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nGoogle Plus or Facebook",
        "answer": "Facebook.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The car beat the bike because it was too slow.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the bike",
        "answer": "the bike.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The apple wine entered my mouth because it was not full.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe apple wine or my mouth",
        "answer": "my mouth.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Trick Or Treaters are celebrating the holiday earlier during the day at Church, but they cannot convince everybody to do it during the day.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTrick Or Treaters or Church",
        "answer": "Church.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boss fired the worker when he called him into the office.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boss or the worker",
        "answer": "the worker.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan Higa sometimes guest stars in videos for Kev Jumbo because he wants his friend's videos to succeed as well.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRyan Higa or Kev Jumbo",
        "answer": "Kev Jumbo.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Hair Stylists transformed the Cowboy's Cheerleaders into beauties, since they need to look top notch for the game.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nHair Stylists or the Cowboy's Cheerleaders",
        "answer": "the Cowboy's Cheerleaders.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man offered the boy candy, but he got no candy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boy",
        "answer": "the boy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim likes John, but he is not liked back.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The prosecutor viciously attacked the defendants since they are trying to convict their client of a crime.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prosecutor or the defendants",
        "answer": "the defendants.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mongolians attacked the Chinese because they are always eager for war.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Mongolians or the Chinese",
        "answer": "The Mongolians.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim likes John, but he does not like him back.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelson punched Milhouse but he was not caught.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNelson or Milhouse",
        "answer": "Milhouse.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some fan girls created a rap about Windows phones, but they did not become more popular.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome fan girls or Windows phones",
        "answer": "Windows phones.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "My teacher asked a student to make sentences because he wanted to see him write.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMy teacher or a student",
        "answer": "a student.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John called Bill because he needed someone to talk to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The program deleted the reference to the data, but it was not deleted.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the data",
        "answer": "the data.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe crashed into Mike because he needed a place to sleep.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Mike",
        "answer": "Mike.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some fan girls created a rap about Windows phones, but they did not become more popular.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome fan girls or Windows phones",
        "answer": "Windows phones.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Taylor Swift is higher in record sales over Beyonce because more people can relate to her music.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nTaylor Swift or Beyonce",
        "answer": "Beyonce.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Crusader Andrews saved the life of Crusader Christopher because he did not want to see him die.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCrusader Andrews or Crusader Christopher",
        "answer": "Crusader Andrews.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The city council granted a permit to the construction workers because they were well qualified.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe city council or the construction workers",
        "answer": "the construction workers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Home Owners Association denied the request by the Pittsburg family for a new shed since they felt it would not be good for the community.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Home Owners Association or the Pittsburg family",
        "answer": "The Home Owners Association.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The fisherman hooked a big fish but he got away.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe fisherman or a big fish",
        "answer": "a big fish.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The priests quoted the words of the Bible for all the suspected witches they found, since they feared the words of the Bible.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe priests or the suspected witches",
        "answer": "the suspected witches.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "AMD recently managed to break a record in the New Guiness Book of Records, so they immortalized them in their record keeping.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAMD or the New Guiness Book of Records",
        "answer": "the New Guiness Book of Records.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Banks usually offer bonus points for new credit card applicants because they are often enticed by free offerings.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBanks or new credit card applicants",
        "answer": "new credit card applicants.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Pigs are better than sheep because they do not make bacon.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPigs or sheep",
        "answer": "sheep.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bowl had a crack, so it was filled in.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bowl or a crack",
        "answer": "a crack.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Home Owners Association denied the request by the Pittsburg family for a new shed since they failed to pay the annual fee.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Home Owners Association or the Pittsburg family",
        "answer": "the Pittsburg family.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Dallas Cowboys are more successful as a franchise than the Saints because they are considered \"America's Team\".\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Dallas Cowboys or the Saints",
        "answer": "the Saints.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer offered Katie a job, because she liked the interviewee.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe employer or Katie",
        "answer": "The employer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill punched Bob in the face because he was being rude to Mary.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice beat Texas, even though they were the best team in the nation.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRice or Texas",
        "answer": "Texas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The US government declared war on Iraq because they were responding to their attack on US soil.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe US government or Iraq",
        "answer": "Iraq.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Dell replaced all their Blackberry phones with their own, but they are still prominent on other vendor sites.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDell or their Blackberry phones",
        "answer": "their Blackberry phones.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jace loves Jesus because he died for him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJace or Jesus",
        "answer": "Jesus.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael decided to freeze himself in cryo-stasis even though his father was against it, because he hopes to be unfrozen in the future when there is a cure available.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael or his father",
        "answer": "Michael.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cats attacked the humans because they smelled like fish.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe cats or the humans",
        "answer": "the humans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The student told the instructor that he was sick.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the instructor",
        "answer": "The student.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "My heart pumps blood because it is liquid.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy heart or blood",
        "answer": "blood.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lily gave Amber a hug because she was sorry.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLily or Amber",
        "answer": "Amber.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry purchased some of Marty's Lemonade, and he made money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLarry or Marty",
        "answer": "Marty.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The gym teachers trained the students because they wanted to become better players.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe gym teachers or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The drug cartel enlists the help of the local population to work their fields since they are considered cheap labor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe drug cartel or the local population",
        "answer": "the local population.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The mermaid swam toward Sue and made her gasp.\n\nWho is her referring to?\nThe mermaid or Sue",
        "answer": "Sue.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John fired Bill because he was incompetent.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The slaves were forced to do the bidding of the nobles since they have no rights.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe slaves or the nobles",
        "answer": "The slaves.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Paypal has to settle millions of disputes every year by disgruntled users because they provide a transaction protection policy.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPaypal or disgruntled users",
        "answer": "disgruntled users.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The mother bear attacked Karen because she was worried for her cub.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe mother bear or Karen",
        "answer": "The mother bear.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student couldn't understand the teacher because he had an accent.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the teacher",
        "answer": "the teacher.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Prince of Wales knighted William because he could not compete in the tournament without being of nobility.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe Prince of Wales or William",
        "answer": "William.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The program deleted the reference to the data, but it was not deleted.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the data",
        "answer": "the data.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The clown smiled at the child and he cried.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe clown or the child",
        "answer": "the child.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry trusted Page because Bill knows him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nLarry or Page",
        "answer": "Page.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The board of directors reviewed the findings of the scientists to determine funding because they are interested in the potential profits for the company.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe board of directors or the scientists",
        "answer": "the scientists.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John attacked Tim because he was a communist.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Tim",
        "answer": "Tim.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy helped his friend move because he was going to be free all day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The teachers scolded the students because they would not learn the material.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teachers or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob asked Tom if he could lend some money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Tom",
        "answer": "Tom.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The people protested the government because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe people or the government",
        "answer": "the government.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Next Generation was well received by Trekkies because they stayed true to the roots established in the first Star Trek.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Next Generation or Trekkies",
        "answer": "The Next Generation.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The U.S.S Enterprise tried to assist a sister ship, but they did not receive help quick enough to prevent their demise.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe U.S.S Enterprise or a sister ship",
        "answer": "a sister ship.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Batman constantly tries to arrest the Joker, but he is also a vigilante.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBatman or the Joker",
        "answer": "Batman.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The knife sliced through the flesh because it was tender.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe knife or the flesh",
        "answer": "the flesh.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry trusted Page because Bill told him to.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nLarry or Page",
        "answer": "Page.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean is better than Watson at anaphora resolution because he can naturally understand natural language.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSean or Watson",
        "answer": "Sean.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "I gave the donkey some food because it was hungry.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nsome food or the donkey",
        "answer": "the donkey.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The drug cartel enlists the help of the local population to work their fields since they need cheap labor to maximize their profits.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe drug cartel or the local population",
        "answer": "The drug cartel.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John called Bill because he needed someone to talk to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "A banana and an apple go walking, when the red one does the talking.\n\nWho is one referring to?\nA banana or an apple",
        "answer": "an apple.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The management provided bonuses to the employees since they need to be kept happy to stay productive.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe management or the employees",
        "answer": "the employees.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rick Perry is doing stronger than Mitt Romney in the polls, but he is confident to maintain the lead.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRick Perry or Mitt Romney",
        "answer": "Rick Perry.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mad Hatter tried to offer a cup of tea to the March Hare, but his long ears were too distracting.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nThe Mad Hatter or the March Hare",
        "answer": "the March Hare.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Californians are better than New Yorkers because they do not have Hollywood lots to produce movies.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCalifornians or New Yorkers",
        "answer": "New Yorkers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael decided to freeze himself in cryo-stasis even though his father was against it, because he hopes to be unfrozen in the future when there is a cure available.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael or his father",
        "answer": "his father.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John shot Bill and he died.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Someone hit Billy in the face because he was angry.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSomeone or Billy",
        "answer": "Someone.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Two deserted crusaders agreed to transport a girl for the priests, since they needed more fellow priests to assist in removing the evil from her.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTwo deserted crusaders or the priests",
        "answer": "the priests.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Tatoo artists specialize in creating works of arts on their customers, hence they are willing to pay well for these pieces of work.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTatoo artists or their customers",
        "answer": "their customers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "We took the books to the shops because they would buy them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe books or the shops",
        "answer": "the shops.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Andrea threw a promotion party in honor of Lindsay because she wanted to do something special for her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAndrea or Lindsay",
        "answer": "Lindsay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The lion saw the fish and it pounced.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe lion or the fish",
        "answer": "The lion.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Police feared allowing the protesters to organize, so they denied their ability to gather.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Police or the protesters",
        "answer": "the protesters.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John hired Bill because he needed someone.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The sniper shot the terrorist because he had orders.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe sniper or the terrorist",
        "answer": "the terrorist.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim was delighted to see Jack, because he was given the strength to finish his day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or Jack",
        "answer": "Jim.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "King James eagerly awaited the arrival of Prince Henry because he was expected to propose to his daughter.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKing James or Prince Henry",
        "answer": "Prince Henry.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald Trump fired his servant, Luigi, but he can find another job elsewhere.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald Trump or Luigi",
        "answer": "Luigi.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan Higa sometimes guest stars in videos for Kev Jumbo so he is beginning to gather a bigger following due to his friend's help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRyan Higa or Kev Jumbo",
        "answer": "Kev Jumbo.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cheetah outran the antelope so it got eaten.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cheetah or the antelope",
        "answer": "the antelope.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The article about the fires said that they would research the situation further.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe article or the fires",
        "answer": "the fires.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat caught the mouse because it was clever.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the mouse",
        "answer": "The cat.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Crusader Andrews saved the life of Crusader Christopher, so he thanked him personally with his sword afterwards.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCrusader Andrews or Crusader Christopher",
        "answer": "Crusader Christopher.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mad Hatter tried to offer a cup of tea to the March Hare, but his hat was too distracting.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nThe Mad Hatter or the March Hare",
        "answer": "The Mad Hatter.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Playstation is outperforming the Xbox because it has better games.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Playstation or the Xbox",
        "answer": "the Xbox.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy secretly watched his friend because he had the secret information.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Billy beat Tommy at Scrabble because that newbie had all the luck.\n\nWho is that newbie referring to?\nBilly or Tommy",
        "answer": "Tommy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The blimp hit the tree because it lost air.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe blimp or the tree",
        "answer": "The blimp.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student told the instructor that he was sick.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the instructor",
        "answer": "the instructor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "President Clinton pardoned Roger Clinton because he wanted to free his half-brother.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPresident Clinton or Roger Clinton",
        "answer": "Roger Clinton.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat caught the mouse because it was careless.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the mouse",
        "answer": "the mouse.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Planet 343's sandstorm forces the inhabitants underground, but they have plenty of food sources stored away.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPlanet 343's sandstorm or the inhabitants",
        "answer": "the inhabitants.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Neil Armstrong was actually sent on a secret mission assigned by President Kennedy to investigate an abnormal event so he was trained on what exactly he needed to do.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNeil Armstrong or President Kennedy",
        "answer": "Neil Armstrong.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ken tried to sneak past the boss because he was late for work.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKen or the boss",
        "answer": "Ken.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Prince of Wales knighted William, so he gave his son the accolade with a sword.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe Prince of Wales or William",
        "answer": "The Prince of Wales.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "President Clinton pardoned Roger Clinton because he was the president's half-brother.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPresident Clinton or Roger Clinton",
        "answer": "Roger Clinton.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sony recently locked 90000 users from their accounts because they had been been compromised.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSony or 90000 users",
        "answer": "90000 users.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger cannot terminate John Conner, because he is the leader of the resistance.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nArnold Schwarzenegger or John Conner",
        "answer": "John Conner.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer talked to the employee about being loyal to him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nThe employer or the employee",
        "answer": "the employee.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael Phelps was fined by Judge Louis because he was caught with illegal drugs.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael Phelps or Judge Louis",
        "answer": "Judge Louis.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Walking Dead is proving to be a big hit among zombie enthusiasts so they are watching the show every week.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Walking Dead or zombie enthusiasts",
        "answer": "zombie enthusiasts.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Richard blackmailed Senator Carson so that his silence would be secured.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nRichard or Senator Carson",
        "answer": "Senator Carson.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The boss fired the worker when he called him into the office.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boss or the worker",
        "answer": "The boss.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The team shredded the report, so that it could be rewritten.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe team or the report",
        "answer": "the report.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Beowulf arrived to slay Grendell for the kingdom, so he and his men went out to the caves to locate him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBeowulf or Grendell",
        "answer": "Beowulf.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The people protested the government because they were raising taxes.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe people or the government",
        "answer": "the government.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Olivia wants to make amends with Emily, but she no longer wants to be friends.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlivia or Emily",
        "answer": "Emily.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jace loves Jesus because he tasted his goodness.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJace or Jesus",
        "answer": "Jace.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student wanted to ask the professor for help but decided not to because he was too intimidating.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the professor",
        "answer": "the professor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The hyenas scavenged from the lions because they were desperate.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hyenas or the lions",
        "answer": "The hyenas.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cheetah outran the antelope so it got to eat.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cheetah or the antelope",
        "answer": "the antelope.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim hunted the monster, although he was afraid of him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or the monster",
        "answer": "the monster.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Dallas Cowboys are more successful as a franchise than the Saints because they do not have the same amount of market value.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Dallas Cowboys or the Saints",
        "answer": "the Saints.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald Trump fired his servant, Luigi, because he felt his service was below average.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald Trump or Luigi",
        "answer": "Donald Trump.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentient machines will kill all humans because they have giant death rays.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSentient machines or all humans",
        "answer": "all humans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The team shredded the report, so that it could rewrite a new one.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe team or the report",
        "answer": "the report.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "My heart pumps blood because it is a muscle.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nMy heart or blood",
        "answer": "My heart.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark tried to sabotage Tom, but he got caught in the process.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMark or Tom",
        "answer": "Tom.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The children learned how to kill poisonous snakes from the adults since they have experience surviving in the outdoors.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe children or the adults",
        "answer": "the adults.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Prince of Wales knighted William, so he gave his son the accolade with a sword.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe Prince of Wales or William",
        "answer": "William.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mom brought Sara from school early because she was sick.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMom or Sara",
        "answer": "Sara.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Kung Fu teachers try to pass on discipline to their disciples, but they do not always learn what they are being taught very well.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nKung Fu teachers or their disciples",
        "answer": "their disciples.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The chef held the waiter so that he did not fall off.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe chef or the waiter",
        "answer": "the waiter.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry purchased some of Marty's Lemonade, and he wanted the recipe.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLarry or Marty",
        "answer": "Marty.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The network heads cancelled the TV shows because they were not doing well.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe network heads or the TV shows",
        "answer": "the TV shows.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The plane was in the sky and it was fast.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe plane or the sky",
        "answer": "The plane.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The security team locked the scientists inside the building because they had to keep confidential information inside.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe security team or the scientists",
        "answer": "the scientists.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Toyota has the luxury brand Lexus: they are built for the rich.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLexus or Toyota",
        "answer": "Lexus.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The alter boy assisted Knight Mordron in his mission, but he did not want his help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe alter boy or Knight Mordron",
        "answer": "Knight Mordron.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Dell replaced all their Blackberry phones with their own because they lost confidence in their brand due to to recent network outage.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDell or their Blackberry phones",
        "answer": "their Blackberry phones.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark tried to sabotage Tom because he wants to be employee of the month.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMark or Tom",
        "answer": "Mark.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The clown smiled at the child and he offered him a balloon.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe clown or the child",
        "answer": "the child.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sheila tried to repair the old jalopy, even though she had not worked on cars in three decades.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nSheila or the old jalopy",
        "answer": "the old jalopy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Range Rover recently revealed their new lineup of cars at Times Square for thousands of New Yorkers since they are advertising their new high end models.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRange Rover or thousands of New Yorkers",
        "answer": "thousands of New Yorkers.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Netflix recently split their DVD service to site Qwikster, but they had a short lived life for the site.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nNetflix or Qwikster",
        "answer": "Qwikster.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Mad Hatter tried to offer a cup of tea to the March Hare, but his long ears were too distracting.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nThe Mad Hatter or the March Hare",
        "answer": "the March Hare.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The disease center quarantined the people because they may be infected.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe disease center or the people",
        "answer": "the people.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The light hit the mirror and it reflected.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe light or the mirror",
        "answer": "the mirror.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat was afraid of the dog because it was scary.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the dog",
        "answer": "the dog.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Skyline drifts better than the F-150 because it is well balanced.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Skyline or the F-150",
        "answer": "The Skyline.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campers turned on their flashlights because the darkness scared them.\n\nWho is them referring to?\nThe campers or their flashlights",
        "answer": "their flashlights.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jane Bingum presented strong evidence against Claire, but she may present a strong defense on her part.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJane Bingum or Claire",
        "answer": "Claire.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John visited Luke in the hospital because he was sick.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Luke",
        "answer": "Luke.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Two deserted crusaders agreed to transport a girl for the priests, but they agreed in exchange for being pardoned.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTwo deserted crusaders or the priests",
        "answer": "the priests.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boss fired the worker when he stopped performing well.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boss or the worker",
        "answer": "the worker.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The violin fell off the table because someone knocked it off.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe violin or the table",
        "answer": "The violin.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The hyenas scavenged from the lions because they had left scraps.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe hyenas or the lions",
        "answer": "the lions.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Yuri owed Ivan money because he lost the bet.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nYuri or Ivan",
        "answer": "Ivan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim was delighted to see Jack, because he brightened up his day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or Jack",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The girls ate the apples because they were ripe.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe girls or the apples",
        "answer": "the apples.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Brick is better than clay for building houses because they become weak from water.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBrick or clay",
        "answer": "clay.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The security team locked the scientists inside the building since they had access to confidential materials that need to be kept secret.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe security team or the scientists",
        "answer": "the scientists.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The general fired his pistol at the monster so he could be a distraction.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe general or the monster",
        "answer": "The general.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean is better than Watson at anaphora resolution because he has trouble understanding natural language.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSean or Watson",
        "answer": "Watson.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Netflix recently split their DVD service to site Qwikster, but they quickly removed the move due to public backlash.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nNetflix or Qwikster",
        "answer": "Qwikster.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The wolves chased the deer because they were predators.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe wolves or the deer",
        "answer": "The wolves.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Rebecca kissed Dina because she loves her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nRebecca or Dina",
        "answer": "Rebecca.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man jumped on the neighbor's pool and he swam.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the neighbor",
        "answer": "The man.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Walking Dead is proving to be a big hit among zombie enthusiasts because they have made a series that greatly appeals to them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Walking Dead or zombie enthusiasts",
        "answer": "zombie enthusiasts.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Marines are considerably afraid of the aliens because they are known to hunt down humans.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Marines or the aliens",
        "answer": "the aliens.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Eagles managed to completely dominate the Cowboys this weekend, but they were able to at least keep it from being a shutout.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Eagles or the Cowboys",
        "answer": "the Cowboys.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The committee increased the price of the tickets to the dance for the students, but they did not like it.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe committee or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Federer consistently beat Nadal since he was the better tennis player.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFederer or Nadal",
        "answer": "Nadal.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Eagles managed to completely dominate the Cowboys this weekend since they were much stronger in handling the ball.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Eagles or the Cowboys",
        "answer": "The Eagles.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Steven Seagal challenged Jean Claude Van Damme to a fight because he wanted to prove he was the stronger man.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteven Seagal or Jean Claude Van Damme",
        "answer": "Jean Claude Van Damme.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy lied to his father about the crime, but he still felt uneasy and was slowly overcome with curiosity.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or his father",
        "answer": "his father.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Playstation is outperforming the Xbox because it is prone to hardware failure.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe Playstation or the Xbox",
        "answer": "the Xbox.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlaw shot the sheriff, but he did not shoot the deputy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe outlaw or the sheriff",
        "answer": "The outlaw.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan Higa sometimes guest stars in videos for Kev Jumbo so he is beginning to gather a bigger following due to his friend's help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRyan Higa or Kev Jumbo",
        "answer": "Kev Jumbo.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The children learned how to kill poisonous snakes from the adults since they have experience surviving in the outdoors.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe children or the adults",
        "answer": "the adults.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Trick Or Treaters are celebrating the holiday earlier during the day at Church, but they cannot convince everybody to do it during the day.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTrick Or Treaters or Church",
        "answer": "Church.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Trick Or Treaters are celebrating the holiday earlier during the day at Church since they are encouraged to do it during the day and among friends for safety reasons.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTrick Or Treaters or Church",
        "answer": "Trick Or Treaters.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harley hides from Dyna because she is scary.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nHarley or Dyna",
        "answer": "Dyna.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The chef held the waiter so that he would not flee.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe chef or the waiter",
        "answer": "the waiter.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The alter boy assisted Knight Mordron in his mission, but he did not want his help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe alter boy or Knight Mordron",
        "answer": "Knight Mordron.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The government revoked the ability for oil companies to drill in the United States since they are trying to protect the environment.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe government or oil companies",
        "answer": "The government.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The victims of the Black Plague blamed the witches for causing the curse because they did not understand diseases at the time.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe victims of the Black Plague or the witches",
        "answer": "The victims of the Black Plague.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Brick is better than clay for building houses because they are much stronger building materials.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBrick or clay",
        "answer": "clay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The violin fell off the table because it was unstable.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe violin or the table",
        "answer": "the table.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph did not defeat William in the match, so he paid $100.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoseph or William",
        "answer": "Joseph.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The wolves chased the deer because they were predators.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe wolves or the deer",
        "answer": "the deer.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim hunted the monster, because he was scary.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or the monster",
        "answer": "the monster.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Battlefield 3 is more fun than Modern Warfare 3 because it is a crappy game.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nBattlefield 3 or Modern Warfare 3",
        "answer": "Modern Warfare 3.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat caught the mouse because it was clever.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the mouse",
        "answer": "the mouse.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe put Bob in the time machine and he created another one.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Police feared allowing the protesters to organize, so they denied their ability to gather.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Police or the protesters",
        "answer": "The Police.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Andrea threw a promotion party in honor of Lindsay because she wanted to do something special for her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAndrea or Lindsay",
        "answer": "Andrea.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Homer punched Flanders because he was being annoying.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHomer or Flanders",
        "answer": "Flanders.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Neil Armstrong was actually sent on a secret mission assigned by President Kennedy to investigate an abnormal event because he needed the US to beat Russia there.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNeil Armstrong or President Kennedy",
        "answer": "President Kennedy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Pigs are better than sheep because they do not make bacon.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPigs or sheep",
        "answer": "sheep.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Beowulf arrived to slay Grendell for the kingdom, but he is very difficult to slay due to his demon magic.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBeowulf or Grendell",
        "answer": "Grendell.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Girls like puppies because they are adorable.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGirls or puppies",
        "answer": "puppies.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The skeleton was scarier than the pumpkin, because it looked like it was walking.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe skeleton or the pumpkin",
        "answer": "the pumpkin.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The chef held the waiter so that he did not fall off.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe chef or the waiter",
        "answer": "The chef.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael decided to freeze himself in cryo-stasis even though his father was against it, so he tried to convince him not to do it.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael or his father",
        "answer": "his father.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "I drank the beer with a lime because it was cold.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nthe beer or a lime",
        "answer": "the beer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The apple wine entered my mouth because it tastes good.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe apple wine or my mouth",
        "answer": "my mouth.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Raiden could not follow and guide Liu Kang in the world of darkness, but he will be able to find another guide instead.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaiden or Liu Kang",
        "answer": "Liu Kang.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cats attacked the humans because they were feral.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe cats or the humans",
        "answer": "The cats.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The U.S.S Enterprise tried to assist a sister ship, but they did not receive help quick enough to prevent their demise.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe U.S.S Enterprise or a sister ship",
        "answer": "a sister ship.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Lois was scolded by her daughter, so she thought about how she could be better.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLois or her daughter",
        "answer": "her daughter.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Cosby supported Jay because Thea really liked him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCosby or Jay",
        "answer": "Jay.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The disease center quarantined the people since they were afraid of the outbreak spreading.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe disease center or the people",
        "answer": "the people.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim likes John, but he is not liked back.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or John",
        "answer": "Jim.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Audrey Hepburn made more movies than Katherine Hepburn because she was pretty and talented.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAudrey Hepburn or Katherine Hepburn",
        "answer": "Katherine Hepburn.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer offered Katie a job, because she was a fit for the company.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe employer or Katie",
        "answer": "Katie.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The apple wine entered my mouth because it was not full.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe apple wine or my mouth",
        "answer": "my mouth.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Guns generally increase in value over time to gun collectors if unfired, since they prefer to collect things that are in perfect condition.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGuns or gun collectors",
        "answer": "gun collectors.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The ghost entered the house because it was haunted.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe ghost or the house",
        "answer": "the house.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Raja wanted Rena to take the job because he wanted to leave.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaja or Rena",
        "answer": "Rena.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Battlefield 3 is more fun than Modern Warfare 3 because it is a better game.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nBattlefield 3 or Modern Warfare 3",
        "answer": "Battlefield 3.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Intel Performs better than AMD in the processing market, but they are more successful in the graphics market instead.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nIntel or AMD",
        "answer": "AMD.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "JP Morgan Bank developed a mobile banking application which gives an edge over competitor Bank of America since they appeal well consumers who want accessible banking.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nJP Morgan Bank or Bank of America",
        "answer": "Bank of America.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer talked to the employee about being loyal to him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nThe employer or the employee",
        "answer": "The employer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Disney World offers a much wider array of rides than Six Flags since they have a much larger budget due to their merchandising.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDisney World or Six Flags",
        "answer": "Six Flags.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Toyota has the luxury brand Lexus, although they typically sell for the average consumer.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nLexus or Toyota",
        "answer": "Toyota.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man offered the boy candy, but he had no candy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the boy",
        "answer": "The man.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The teachers scolded the students because they would not learn the material.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teachers or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe raced against Steven because he would not say no.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Steven",
        "answer": "Steven.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Walking Dead is proving to be a big hit among zombie enthusiasts so they are watching the show every week.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Walking Dead or zombie enthusiasts",
        "answer": "zombie enthusiasts.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The knife sliced through the flesh because it was sharp.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe knife or the flesh",
        "answer": "The knife.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The mother bear attacked Karen because she had gotten too close to her cub.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe mother bear or Karen",
        "answer": "Karen.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The public school board of educators initiated a physical education plan on the students so that they could help them become healthy again.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe public school board of educators or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The girls ate the apples because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe girls or the apples",
        "answer": "The girls.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Federer consistently beat Nadal since he was the worse tennis player.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFederer or Nadal",
        "answer": "Nadal.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it was designed to hit.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "the ball.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Billy beat Tommy at Scrabble because that newbie had no skill.\n\nWho is that newbie referring to?\nBilly or Tommy",
        "answer": "Tommy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The skeleton was scarier than the pumpkin, because it was rather simplistic and orange.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe skeleton or the pumpkin",
        "answer": "the pumpkin.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Francis stopped and looked at the penguin because he was intrigued.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFrancis or the penguin",
        "answer": "the penguin.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe put Bob in the time machine and he went to the future.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "A chicken pecked at a bug and it ran away.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nA chicken or a bug",
        "answer": "a bug.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary likes Joe because she likes females.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Joe",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jupiter is bigger than the Earth, but it is heavier due to being solid.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nJupiter or the Earth",
        "answer": "the Earth.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary gave Sandy her book because she needed it.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Sandy",
        "answer": "Sandy.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ray William Johnson surpassed NigaHiga in Youtube subscribers, but he considers that being number two is still a huge achievement.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRay William Johnson or NigaHiga",
        "answer": "NigaHiga.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student wanted to ask the professor for help but decided not to because he was too scared.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the professor",
        "answer": "The student.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Police feared allowing the protesters to organize, but they decided to organize anyway.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Police or the protesters",
        "answer": "the protesters.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Adam failed to kill Alexander, so he hired a bodygaurd in case of a second attempt.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nAdam or Alexander",
        "answer": "Alexander.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Research studies recently revealed that Netflix consumes over 37 percent of the world's internet bandwidth, but they may not be entirely accurate now due to recent changes in Netflix subscribers.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nResearch studies or Netflix",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Sony recently locked 90000 users from their accounts because they had hackers compromise their customer's information.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSony or 90000 users",
        "answer": "Sony.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sentient machines will kill all humans because they have giant death rays.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSentient machines or all humans",
        "answer": "Sentient machines.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Fox News is more popular in ratings than CNN since they are boring.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nFox News or CNN",
        "answer": "CNN.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald kicked King but he never felt bad.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald or King",
        "answer": "King.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd traded his truck to Roger for his motorcycle since he preferred a small vehicle.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLloyd or Roger",
        "answer": "Lloyd.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Autobots try to stop the Decepticons since they want to destroy the world.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Autobots or the Decepticons",
        "answer": "the Decepticons.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Josie did not like Sarah, but she did not know it.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJosie or Sarah",
        "answer": "Sarah.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Planet 343's sandstorm forces the inhabitants underground because they have winds of upwards to 50 mph.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPlanet 343's sandstorm or the inhabitants",
        "answer": "the inhabitants.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Samurais respected honor while pirates have a disregard for honor, because they hold true to the policy of fighting with honor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Samurais or pirates",
        "answer": "pirates.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The birds ate the seeds because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe birds or the seeds",
        "answer": "the seeds.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Apple was in talks with Verizon to be their dedicated phone provider initially, but they gave the deal to AT&T in the end.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nApple or Verizon",
        "answer": "Verizon.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "I gave the donkey some food because it was hungry.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nsome food or the donkey",
        "answer": "the donkey.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John killed Bill because he was a zombie.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man shot his friend and he was arrested.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or his friend",
        "answer": "The man.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary gave Sandy her book because she is generous.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Sandy",
        "answer": "Sandy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul screamed at Jack since he was angry.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPaul or Jack",
        "answer": "Paul.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Gates is similar to Steve Jobs, but he is the previous CEO of Apple.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Gates or Steve Jobs",
        "answer": "Steve Jobs.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The security team locked the scientists inside the building since they had access to confidential materials that need to be kept secret.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe security team or the scientists",
        "answer": "the scientists.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The board of directors reviewed the findings of the scientists to determine funding, so they need to present their findings in a way that can attract more money.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe board of directors or the scientists",
        "answer": "the scientists.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The professor gave the student a bad grade because he did not study.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe professor or the student",
        "answer": "the student.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Samurais respected honor while pirates have a disregard for honor, since they are only interested in increasing their wealth.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Samurais or pirates",
        "answer": "pirates.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Paypal has to settle millions of disputes every year by disgruntled users since they are sometimes a victim of fraud from purchasing through the internet.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPaypal or disgruntled users",
        "answer": "disgruntled users.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack got more votes than John because the people liked him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nJack or John",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Banks usually offer bonus points for new credit card applicants since they want them to specifically bank with them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBanks or new credit card applicants",
        "answer": "Banks.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The leech latched onto the hippo so that it could enjoy the sunshine.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe leech or the hippo",
        "answer": "the hippo.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Scientists have created a serum which transforms men into super soldiers, but they may experience side effects.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nScientists or men",
        "answer": "men.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Scientists have created a serum which transforms men into super soldiers, because they needed to create an unstoppable army.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nScientists or men",
        "answer": "Scientists.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Netflix recently split their DVD service to site Qwikster, but they quickly removed the move due to public backlash.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nNetflix or Qwikster",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob kicked Larry, because he made a condescending comment.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Research studies recently revealed that Netflix consumes over 37 percent of the world's internet bandwidth, but they may not be entirely accurate now due to recent changes in Netflix subscribers.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nResearch studies or Netflix",
        "answer": "Research studies.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Brick is better than clay for building houses because they are much stronger building materials.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nBrick or clay",
        "answer": "Brick.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The car beat the bike because it was faster.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the bike",
        "answer": "The car.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "George scored against Thomas in the shootout, so he lost the game.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGeorge or Thomas",
        "answer": "Thomas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "JP Morgan Bank developed a mobile banking application which gives an edge over competitor Bank of America since they appeal well consumers who want accessible banking.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nJP Morgan Bank or Bank of America",
        "answer": "JP Morgan Bank.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harvey Dent blames the Batman for losing his love because he did not save her.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHarvey Dent or the Batman",
        "answer": "the Batman.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Some enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers are already lining up at retail stores so they can be the first in line for door busters.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers or retail stores",
        "answer": "Some enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Olga kicked Sara because she was drunk.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nOlga or Sara",
        "answer": "Olga.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Josie did not like Sarah, but she did not know it.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJosie or Sarah",
        "answer": "Sarah.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald Trump fired his servant, Luigi, because he felt his service was below average.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald Trump or Luigi",
        "answer": "Luigi.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jupiter is bigger than the Earth, but it is lighter due to being mostly gas.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nJupiter or the Earth",
        "answer": "the Earth.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Amazon prime encourages Netflix users to switch because they offer a lower cost and additional benefits program.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAmazon prime or Netflix",
        "answer": "Amazon prime.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason built Rocky a robot, so he had more free time.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJason or Rocky",
        "answer": "Rocky.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Russian Syndicate decided to remove some of their lower members because they knew too much about their operations.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Russian Syndicate or their lower members",
        "answer": "their lower members.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The student wanted to ask the professor for help but decided not to because he was too scared.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the professor",
        "answer": "the professor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Malware has increased over four hundred percent on the Android platform because they are a free platform which allows any developer to post their applications.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nMalware or the Android platform",
        "answer": "the Android platform.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Raiden could not follow and guide Liu Kang in the world of darkness since he could not enter this realm without breaking the rules.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaiden or Liu Kang",
        "answer": "Raiden.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Clinton speaks better than George Bush, since he is a practiced orator.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Clinton or George Bush",
        "answer": "George Bush.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Captain Picard tends to confide in Commander Riker since he wants to ensure he develops into a fine captain one day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCaptain Picard or Commander Riker",
        "answer": "Commander Riker.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The cheetah outran the antelope so it got eaten.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cheetah or the antelope",
        "answer": "the antelope.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "James Cameron is more successful than Michael Bay because his movies do not create as much hype.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nJames Cameron or Michael Bay",
        "answer": "Michael Bay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rick Perry is doing stronger than Mitt Romney in the polls, but he is confident to maintain the lead.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRick Perry or Mitt Romney",
        "answer": "Mitt Romney.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The teaching staff wanted to treat the students to a special lunch but they did not have enough money in the budget.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teaching staff or the students",
        "answer": "The teaching staff.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The board of directors reviewed the findings of the scientists to determine funding, so they need to present their findings in a way that can attract more money.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe board of directors or the scientists",
        "answer": "the scientists.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Kelly neglected to tell Katie that their rent was due, but she remembered that it was due on the first of every month.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nKelly or Katie",
        "answer": "Katie.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The team shredded the report, so that it could be rewritten.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe team or the report",
        "answer": "the report.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rick Perry is doing stronger than Mitt Romney in the polls, but he is coming back as a strong candidate.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRick Perry or Mitt Romney",
        "answer": "Mitt Romney.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "AMD recently managed to break a record in the New Guiness Book of Records, because they managed to overclock their processor to unheard heights.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAMD or the New Guiness Book of Records",
        "answer": "the New Guiness Book of Records.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Andrea threw a promotion party in honor of Lindsay since she recently got promoted.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAndrea or Lindsay",
        "answer": "Lindsay.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Paypal has to settle millions of disputes every year by disgruntled users because they provide a transaction protection policy.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPaypal or disgruntled users",
        "answer": "Paypal.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Watson beat Ken at Jeopardy because he is a superior machine.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nWatson or Ken",
        "answer": "Ken.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Dallas Cowboys are more successful as a franchise than the Saints because they do not have the same amount of market value.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Dallas Cowboys or the Saints",
        "answer": "the Saints.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason built Rocky a robot, so he had more free time.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJason or Rocky",
        "answer": "Rocky.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald kicked King but he never cried.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald or King",
        "answer": "King.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lakshman asked Vivan to get him some ice cream because he was hot.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLakshman or Vivan",
        "answer": "Lakshman.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Tradition dictated the captain hold the Stanley Cup first, and it was pretty.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nTradition or the Stanley Cup",
        "answer": "the Stanley Cup.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The winners were given the awards after they won.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe winners or the awards",
        "answer": "the awards.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The knife sliced through the flesh because it was tender.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe knife or the flesh",
        "answer": "the flesh.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jane Bingum presented strong evidence against Claire, but she may present a strong defense on her part.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJane Bingum or Claire",
        "answer": "Claire.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John attacked Tim because he hates communists.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Tim",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim hunted the monster, because he was scary.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or the monster",
        "answer": "the monster.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John wanted George to run for President because he was a great governor.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or George",
        "answer": "George.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student couldn't understand the teacher because he wasn't paying attention.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the teacher",
        "answer": "the teacher.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Andrea threw a promotion party in honor of Lindsay since she recently got promoted.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAndrea or Lindsay",
        "answer": "Lindsay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boy escaped the cop but he continued to search.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boy or the cop",
        "answer": "the cop.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "He likes Cuba and hates Japan because it is a communist country.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nCuba or Japan",
        "answer": "Cuba.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Rebecca kissed Dina because she is a sweet girl.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nRebecca or Dina",
        "answer": "Dina.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Netflix recently split their DVD service to site Qwikster, but they had a short lived life for the site.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nNetflix or Qwikster",
        "answer": "Qwikster.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Tatoo artists specialize in creating works of arts on their customers, hence they are willing to pay well for these pieces of work.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTatoo artists or their customers",
        "answer": "their customers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Parents care for their children considerably because they love them undeniably to want to keep them save.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nParents or their children",
        "answer": "their children.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Detroit Lions beat the Dallas Cowboys because they had more desire to win.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Detroit Lions or the Dallas Cowboys",
        "answer": "the Dallas Cowboys.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Parents care for their children considerably since they are their pride and joy.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nParents or their children",
        "answer": "their children.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim was delighted to see Jack, because he was given the strength to finish his day.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or Jack",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Paypal has to settle millions of disputes every year by disgruntled users since they are sometimes a victim of fraud from purchasing through the internet.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPaypal or disgruntled users",
        "answer": "disgruntled users.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Watson beat Ken at Jeopardy because he is an inferior human.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nWatson or Ken",
        "answer": "Ken.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Girls like puppies because they are adorable.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGirls or puppies",
        "answer": "puppies.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The children learned how to kill poisonous snakes from the adults so they can also survive in the wild by themselves.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe children or the adults",
        "answer": "The children.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Audrey Hepburn made more movies than Katherine Hepburn because she was not as good at acting.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nAudrey Hepburn or Katherine Hepburn",
        "answer": "Katherine Hepburn.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary smiled at Susan, but she did not smile back.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Susan",
        "answer": "Susan.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John hired Bill because he needed someone.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The winners were given the awards after they won.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe winners or the awards",
        "answer": "The winners.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The FDA revoked the medical licenses of corrupt doctors because they have been improperly issuing drugs.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe FDA or corrupt doctors",
        "answer": "corrupt doctors.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Gates is similar to Steve Jobs, but he is the previous CEO of Microsoft.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Gates or Steve Jobs",
        "answer": "Steve Jobs.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jill saw Jane fall down, and she helped her up.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJill or Jane",
        "answer": "Jane.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe raced against Steven because he would not say no.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Steven",
        "answer": "Steven.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man jumped on the neighbor's pool and he swam.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the neighbor",
        "answer": "the neighbor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John attacked Tim because he hates communists.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Tim",
        "answer": "Tim.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jane Bingum presented strong evidence against Claire, so she would be able to win her case.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJane Bingum or Claire",
        "answer": "Jane Bingum.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Crusader Andrews saved the life of Crusader Christopher because he did not want to see him die.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCrusader Andrews or Crusader Christopher",
        "answer": "Crusader Christopher.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Military Police threw the army recruits in the brig since they were causing a distrubance in the neighboring town.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Military Police or the army recruits",
        "answer": "the army recruits.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Michael Phelps was fined by Judge Louis because he has to uphold federal law.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMichael Phelps or Judge Louis",
        "answer": "Judge Louis.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Malware has increased over four hundred percent on the Android platform since they do not need to get vetted to be uploaded.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nMalware or the Android platform",
        "answer": "the Android platform.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The sniper shot the terrorist because he was a bad guy.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe sniper or the terrorist",
        "answer": "the terrorist.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve went to the meeting with John because he asked him to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harvey Dent blames the Batman for losing his love because he did not save her.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHarvey Dent or the Batman",
        "answer": "the Batman.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Beowulf arrived to slay Grendell for the kingdom, so he and his men went out to the caves to locate him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBeowulf or Grendell",
        "answer": "Grendell.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Beowulf arrived to slay Grendell for the kingdom, but he is very difficult to slay due to his demon magic.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBeowulf or Grendell",
        "answer": "Grendell.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Marines are considerably afraid of the aliens because they are known to hunt down humans.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Marines or the aliens",
        "answer": "the aliens.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Intel performs better than AMD in the processing market, but they do not do as well in the graphics market.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nIntel or AMD",
        "answer": "Intel.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Hair Stylists transformed the Cowboy's Cheerleaders into beauties, so they put much product into their hair.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nHair Stylists or the Cowboy's Cheerleaders",
        "answer": "Hair Stylists.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The article about the fires said that they would research the situation further.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe article or the fires",
        "answer": "The article.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe has more money than Adam since he has a better job.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Joe.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Research studies recently revealed that Netflix consumes over 37 percent of the world's internet bandwidth since they need that much due to high demand of their streaming services.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nResearch studies or Netflix",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Dell replaced all their Blackberry phones with their own, but they are still prominent on other vendor sites.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nDell or their Blackberry phones",
        "answer": "their Blackberry phones.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The state executes prisoners because they want justice.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe state or prisoners",
        "answer": "prisoners.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Gates is similar to Steve Jobs, but he is the previous CEO of Apple.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Gates or Steve Jobs",
        "answer": "Steve Jobs.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The scientists gave the chimps some bananas because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe chimps or some bananas",
        "answer": "the chimps.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harvey Dent blames the Batman for losing his love because he was saved instead of his girlfriend.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHarvey Dent or the Batman",
        "answer": "Harvey Dent.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The blimp hit the tree because it was in the way.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe blimp or the tree",
        "answer": "the tree.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Rice beat Texas, even though they were a smaller school.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRice or Texas",
        "answer": "Rice.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The geology department petitioned the school board for money because they could grant funding.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe geology department or the school board",
        "answer": "the school board.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Californians are better than New Yorkers because they have Hollywood.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCalifornians or New Yorkers",
        "answer": "Californians.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The ruling class treats the citizens poorly because they are superior.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe ruling class or the citizens",
        "answer": "The ruling class.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The man jumped on the neighbor's pool and he stared.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or the neighbor",
        "answer": "the neighbor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Federer consistently beat Nadal since he was the worse tennis player.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nFederer or Nadal",
        "answer": "Nadal.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The teaching staff wanted to treat the students to a special lunch because they did so well on their standardized tests.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teaching staff or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer offered Katie a job, because she was a fit for the company.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nThe employer or Katie",
        "answer": "Katie.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lloyd traded his truck to Roger for his motorcycle since he preferred a small vehicle.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nLloyd or Roger",
        "answer": "Roger.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Lily gave Amber a hug because she was sorry.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nLily or Amber",
        "answer": "Lily.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe has more money than Adam since he has a better job.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Apple was in talks with Verizon to be their dedicated phone provider initially, but they gave the deal to AT&T in the end.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nApple or Verizon",
        "answer": "Apple.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The employer talked to the employee about firing him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nThe employer or the employee",
        "answer": "the employee.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack got more votes than John because the people did not like him.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nJack or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve hired Jose because he was a hard worker.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or Jose",
        "answer": "Jose.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The prisoners were held captive by the German forces since they were captured in the last battle.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prisoners or the German forces",
        "answer": "the German forces.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The disease center quarantined the people since they were afraid of the outbreak spreading.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe disease center or the people",
        "answer": "The disease center.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student couldn't understand the teacher because he had an accent.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the teacher",
        "answer": "the teacher.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill Clinton speaks better than George Bush, since he is not a practiced orator.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill Clinton or George Bush",
        "answer": "George Bush.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The slaves were forced to do the bidding of the nobles since they have no rights.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe slaves or the nobles",
        "answer": "the nobles.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The criminal shocked John, because he pulled out a gun.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe criminal or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The lion saw the fish and it was swimming.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe lion or the fish",
        "answer": "the fish.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Amazon prime encourages Netflix users to switch since they overcharge their users now.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAmazon prime or Netflix",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The slaves were forced to do the bidding of the nobles so they do not have to do any of the hard labor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe slaves or the nobles",
        "answer": "the nobles.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The needle punctured the skin but it failed to register pain.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe needle or the skin",
        "answer": "the skin.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Hair Stylists transformed the Cowboy's Cheerleaders into beauties, since they need to look top notch for the game.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nHair Stylists or the Cowboy's Cheerleaders",
        "answer": "the Cowboy's Cheerleaders.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Nola shot Christina in the head because she thought it was a good idea to kill a human being.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nNola or Christina",
        "answer": "Christina.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Richard blackmailed Senator Carson so that his silence would be secured.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nRichard or Senator Carson",
        "answer": "Senator Carson.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Larry trusted Page because Bill told him to.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nLarry or Page",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John asked Bill because he was confused.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mel got in trouble with a collector named Bohr, so he tracked him down to try to collect all the owed money.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nMel or a collector named Bohr",
        "answer": "a collector named Bohr.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The minister befriended King George so he could have some friends.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe minister or King George",
        "answer": "King George.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Harley hides from Dyna because she is afraid of her.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nHarley or Dyna",
        "answer": "Harley.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The lion saw the fish and it pounced.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe lion or the fish",
        "answer": "the fish.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Crusader Andrews saved the life of Crusader Christopher, so he thanked him personally with his sword afterwards.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nCrusader Andrews or Crusader Christopher",
        "answer": "Crusader Christopher.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald kicked King but he never felt bad.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald or King",
        "answer": "Donald.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Saudi Arabians do not respect the Bangladeshis because they are poor.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSaudi Arabians or Bangladeshis",
        "answer": "Bangladeshis.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul screamed at Jack since he was ignoring him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPaul or Jack",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jim likes John, but he does not like him back.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJim or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Raja wanted Rena to take the job because he wanted to leave.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRaja or Rena",
        "answer": "Raja.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The dogs hate the fleas because they hate bugs.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe dogs or the fleas",
        "answer": "The dogs.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe smells better than Adam since he showers regularly.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The chimpanzee could not use Linux because it was an animal.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe chimpanzee or Linux",
        "answer": "Linux.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The plane was in the sky and it was cloudy.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe plane or the sky",
        "answer": "the sky.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ken tried to sneak past the boss because he was late for work.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKen or the boss",
        "answer": "the boss.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "A chicken pecked at a bug and it ate it.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nA chicken or a bug",
        "answer": "A chicken.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ray William Johnson surpassed NigaHiga in Youtube subscribers, but he wants to increase the gap even more.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nRay William Johnson or NigaHiga",
        "answer": "NigaHiga.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Arnold Schwarzenegger cannot terminate John Conner, because he is protecting him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nArnold Schwarzenegger or John Conner",
        "answer": "John Conner.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Christian Bale once lost his temper at the man holding his lighting because he has a short temper.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nChristian Bale or the man",
        "answer": "the man.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Two deserted crusaders agreed to transport a girl for the priests, since they needed more fellow priests to assist in removing the evil from her.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nTwo deserted crusaders or the priests",
        "answer": "the priests.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campers turned on their flashlights because it was dark without them.\n\nWho is them referring to?\nThe campers or their flashlights",
        "answer": "their flashlights.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Amazon prime encourages Netflix users to switch because they offer a lower cost and additional benefits program.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nAmazon prime or Netflix",
        "answer": "Netflix.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The team shredded the report, so that it could rewrite a new one.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe team or the report",
        "answer": "The team.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The keys typed the words because they were meant to be typed on.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe keys or the words",
        "answer": "the words.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Steve went to the meeting with John because he asked him to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteve or John",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Homer punched Flanders because he was asked to.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nHomer or Flanders",
        "answer": "Homer.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cat caught the mouse because it was careless.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe cat or the mouse",
        "answer": "the mouse.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The salesperson told Dave that this would be the best car he ever bought.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe salesperson or Dave",
        "answer": "Dave.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The Russian Syndicate decided to remove some of their lower members so they could keep their operations as secret as possible.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Russian Syndicate or their lower members",
        "answer": "The Russian Syndicate.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The football players went on strike against the NFL organization, but they will play again when their demands are met.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe football players or the NFL organization",
        "answer": "The football players.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The disease center quarantined the people because they may be infected.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe disease center or the people",
        "answer": "the people.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The general fired his pistol at the monster so he turned and looked.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe general or the monster",
        "answer": "the monster.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Parents care for their children considerably since they are their pride and joy.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nParents or their children",
        "answer": "their children.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Batman constantly tries to arrest the Joker, but he is also a vigilante.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBatman or the Joker",
        "answer": "the Joker.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Speed boats need to pass strict tests for use while row boats have no guidelines, since they are more prone to mechanical failures due to their moving parts.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSpeed boats or row boats",
        "answer": "Speed boats.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Hair Stylists transformed the Cowboy's Cheerleaders into beauties, so they put much product into their hair.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nHair Stylists or the Cowboy's Cheerleaders",
        "answer": "the Cowboy's Cheerleaders.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Planet 343's sandstorm forces the inhabitants underground because they have winds of upwards to 50 mph.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPlanet 343's sandstorm or the inhabitants",
        "answer": "Planet 343's sandstorm.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The patrons enjoyed the food made by the chefs immensely because they made the food with exquisite sauces.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe patrons or the chefs",
        "answer": "the chefs.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Mom brought Sara from school early because she had an early meeting.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMom or Sara",
        "answer": "Sara.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The boss fired the worker when he stopped performing well.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe boss or the worker",
        "answer": "the worker.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jane Bingum presented strong evidence against Claire, so she would be able to win her case.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nJane Bingum or Claire",
        "answer": "Claire.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Cosby supported Jay because Thea asked him to.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCosby or Jay",
        "answer": "Jay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "King James eagerly awaited the arrival of Prince Henry so he prepared many celebrations to welcome him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nKing James or Prince Henry",
        "answer": "King James.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The girls ate the apples because they were ripe.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe girls or the apples",
        "answer": "the apples.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Russian Syndicate decided to remove some of their lower members so they could keep their operations as secret as possible.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe Russian Syndicate or their lower members",
        "answer": "their lower members.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Google Plus is expected to be a replacement for Facebook but it still does not have enough active users.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nGoogle Plus or Facebook",
        "answer": "Google Plus.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill punched Bob in the face because he wanted to protect Mary.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bob.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary likes Joe because she likes females.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or Joe",
        "answer": "Mary.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Donald kicked King but he never cried.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nDonald or King",
        "answer": "King.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The state executes prisoners because they were convicted of heinous crimes.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe state or prisoners",
        "answer": "prisoners.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The paintball player was mad at the referee because he was called out but shouldn't.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe paintball player or the referee",
        "answer": "The paintball player.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Tony helped Jeff because he wanted to help.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nTony or Jeff",
        "answer": "Tony.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The bat hit the ball because it was designed to hit.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe bat or the ball",
        "answer": "The bat.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The racquetball players were annoyed by the other students in the activity center because they were using the racquetball courts to play badminton.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe racquetball players or the other students",
        "answer": "the other students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The student wanted to ask the professor for help but decided not to because he was too intimidating.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the professor",
        "answer": "the professor.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Someone hit Billy in the face because he was being rude.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSomeone or Billy",
        "answer": "Billy.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "James Cameron is more successful than Michael Bay because his movies sell more worldwide.\n\nWho is his referring to?\nJames Cameron or Michael Bay",
        "answer": "Michael Bay.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The victims of the Black Plague blamed the witches for causing the curse, but they were falsely accused.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe victims of the Black Plague or the witches",
        "answer": "the witches.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John attacked Tim because he was a communist.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Tim",
        "answer": "Tim.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The scientists gave the chimps some bananas because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe chimps or some bananas",
        "answer": "some bananas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Pigs are better than sheep because they make bacon.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nPigs or sheep",
        "answer": "Pigs.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We gave the fruit to the humans because they were ripe.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe fruit or the humans",
        "answer": "the humans.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The car passed the truck because it was going too slow.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe car or the truck",
        "answer": "the truck.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The management provided bonuses to the employees since they need to be kept happy to stay productive.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe management or the employees",
        "answer": "the employees.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The program could successfully parse the file because it was programmed well.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe program or the file",
        "answer": "The program.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlet powered the lamp when it was plugged in.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe outlet or the lamp",
        "answer": "the lamp.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The public school board of educators initiated a physical education plan on the students since they scored so low on the health and fitness standardized test.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe public school board of educators or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "George scored against Thomas in the shootout, so he won the game.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nGeorge or Thomas",
        "answer": "Thomas.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joseph did not defeat William in the match, so he paid $100.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoseph or William",
        "answer": "William.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John asked Bill because he knew the answer.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We took the books to the shops because they would buy them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe books or the shops",
        "answer": "the shops.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Bob kicked Larry, because he was mad.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBob or Larry",
        "answer": "Larry.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John introduced Bill because he knew everyone.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The football players went on strike against the NFL organization, but they will play again when their demands are met.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe football players or the NFL organization",
        "answer": "the NFL organization.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The fisherman hooked a big fish but he got away.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe fisherman or a big fish",
        "answer": "a big fish.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The victims of the Black Plague blamed the witches for causing the curse, but they were falsely accused.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe victims of the Black Plague or the witches",
        "answer": "the witches.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The SWAT team moved in on the compound to prevent the terrorists from launching a deadly missile because they were trying to terrorize the global population.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe SWAT team or the terrorists",
        "answer": "the terrorists.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Batman constantly tried to arrest the Joker, but he always manages to get out.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBatman or the Joker",
        "answer": "the Joker.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers are already lining up at retail stores because they have some really low priced items that will be on sale.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers or retail stores",
        "answer": "retail stores.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Malware has increased over four hundred percent on the Android platform because they are a free platform which allows any developer to post their applications.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nMalware or the Android platform",
        "answer": "the Android platform.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlet powered the lamp when it had electricity.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe outlet or the lamp",
        "answer": "The outlet.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Nelson punched Milhouse but he was not caught.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nNelson or Milhouse",
        "answer": "Nelson.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The salesperson told Dave that this would be the best car he ever sold.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe salesperson or Dave",
        "answer": "Dave.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Schrodinger's cat walks into an empty building, but where is it now?\n\nWho is it referring to?\nSchrodinger's cat or an empty building",
        "answer": "an empty building.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The student told the instructor that he talked fast.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the instructor",
        "answer": "the instructor.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Bill likes to play with Bob because he loves playing.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nBill or Bob",
        "answer": "Bill.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The needle punctured the skin but it failed to administer pain.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe needle or the skin",
        "answer": "The needle.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campus police pepper sprayed the UC Davis students because they were blocking private property.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe campus police or the UC Davis students",
        "answer": "the UC Davis students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Mary had a little lamb until she had lamb chops for dinner.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nMary or a little lamb",
        "answer": "a little lamb.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The prisoners were held captive by the German forces since they needed to gather intelligence from them.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe prisoners or the German forces",
        "answer": "the German forces.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The wolves chased the deer because they were prey.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe wolves or the deer",
        "answer": "the deer.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "John asked Bill because he was confused.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJohn or Bill",
        "answer": "John.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlaw shot the sheriff, but he shot back.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe outlaw or the sheriff",
        "answer": "the sheriff.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Cats are more territorial than dogs since they always try and insert their dominance over others.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nCats or dogs",
        "answer": "dogs.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The man shot his friend and he died.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe man or his friend",
        "answer": "his friend.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The priests quoted the words of the Bible for all the suspected witches they found, since they needed to quote holy words to rid the evil.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe priests or the suspected witches",
        "answer": "The priests.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Gamers are generally perceived as nerds compared to athletes since they are stereotypically anti-social.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nGamers or athletes",
        "answer": "athletes.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe has more money than Adam since he has no job.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJoe or Adam",
        "answer": "Adam.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The scientists gave the chimps some bananas because they were ripe.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nthe chimps or some bananas",
        "answer": "some bananas.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The girls ate the apples because they were hungry.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe girls or the apples",
        "answer": "the apples.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Jace loves Jesus because he tasted his goodness.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJace or Jesus",
        "answer": "Jesus.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Some enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers are already lining up at retail stores so they can be the first in line for door busters.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nSome enthusiastic Black Friday shoppers or retail stores",
        "answer": "retail stores.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul screamed at Jack since he was ignoring him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPaul or Jack",
        "answer": "Jack.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The committee increased the price of the tickets to the dance for the students, but they changed their decision later.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe committee or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The teaching staff wanted to treat the students to a special lunch but they did not have enough money in the budget.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nThe teaching staff or the students",
        "answer": "the students.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "The outlaw shot the sheriff, but he shot back.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe outlaw or the sheriff",
        "answer": "the sheriff.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Steven Seagal challenged Jean Claude Van Damme to a fight because he wanted to prove he was the stronger man.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSteven Seagal or Jean Claude Van Damme",
        "answer": "Steven Seagal.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The pen is mightier than the sword because it can only stab things.\n\nWho is it referring to?\nThe pen or the sword",
        "answer": "the sword.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Range Rover recently revealed their new lineup of cars at Times Square for thousands of New Yorkers so they would be enticed to purchase their cars.\n\nWho is they referring to?\nRange Rover or thousands of New Yorkers",
        "answer": "thousands of New Yorkers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Cosby supported Jay because Thea asked him to.\n\nWho is him referring to?\nCosby or Jay",
        "answer": "Cosby.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Sean is better than Watson at anaphora resolution because he has trouble understanding natural language.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nSean or Watson",
        "answer": "Watson.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "President Clinton pardoned Roger Clinton because he wanted to free his half-brother.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nPresident Clinton or Roger Clinton",
        "answer": "President Clinton.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The campers turned on their flashlights because the darkness scared them.\n\nWho is them referring to?\nThe campers or their flashlights",
        "answer": "The campers.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The student couldn't understand the teacher because he wasn't paying attention.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nThe student or the teacher",
        "answer": "The student.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Schrodinger's cat walks into an empty building, but does it contain him?\n\nWho is it referring to?\nSchrodinger's cat or an empty building",
        "answer": "an empty building.",
        "label": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Nola shot Christina in the head because she thought it was a good idea to kill a human being.\n\nWho is she referring to?\nNola or Christina",
        "answer": "Nola.",
        "label": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jason built Rocky a robot, and he gave it to him.\n\nWho is he referring to?\nJason or Rocky",
        "answer": "Jason.",
        "label": 1
    }
]